{
	"description": "All jouyou kanji with any valid reading",
	"deck": [
		{ "question": "一", "answers": [ "イチ","イツ","ひと","ひとつ","はじめ" ]},
		{ "question": "丁", "answers": [ "チョウ","テイ","トウ","あたる","ひのと" ]},
		{ "question": "七", "answers": [ "シチ","なな","ななつ","なの","シツ" ]},
		{ "question": "万", "answers": [ "マン","バン","よろず" ]},
		{ "question": "丈", "answers": [ "ジョウ","たけ" ]},
		{ "question": "三", "answers": [ "サン","み","みつ","みっつ" ]},
		{ "question": "上", "answers": [ "ジョウ","あがる","あげる","うえ","うわ","かみ","のぼる","のぼす","のぼせる","ショウ","たてまつる","ほとり" ]},
		{ "question": "下", "answers": [ "カ","ゲ","おりる","おろす","くださる","くだす","くだる","さがる","さげる","した","しも","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "不", "answers": [ "フ","ブ","ず" ]},
		{ "question": "与", "answers": [ "ヨ","あたえる","あずかる","くみする" ]},
		{ "question": "且", "answers": [ "かつ","ショ","しばらく","まさに" ]},
		{ "question": "世", "answers": [ "セ","セイ","よ" ]},
		{ "question": "丘", "answers": [ "キュウ","おか" ]},
		{ "question": "丙", "answers": [ "ヘイ","ひのえ" ]},
		{ "question": "両", "answers": [ "リョウ","ふたつ" ]},
		{ "question": "並", "answers": [ "なみ","ならびに","ならぶ","ならべる","ヘイ" ]},
		{ "question": "中", "answers": [ "ジュウ","チュウ","なか","あたる","あてる" ]},
		{ "question": "串", "answers": [ "くし","カン","セン","つらぬく","なれる" ]},
		{ "question": "丸", "answers": [ "ガン","まる","まるい","まるめる","たま" ]},
		{ "question": "丹", "answers": [ "タン","あか","に","まごころ" ]},
		{ "question": "主", "answers": [ "シュ","おも","ぬし","ス","あるじ","つかさどる" ]},
		{ "question": "丼", "answers": [ "どん","どんぶり","セイ","ショウ","タン","トン" ]},
		{ "question": "久", "answers": [ "キュウ","ひさしい","ク" ]},
		{ "question": "乏", "answers": [ "ボウ","とぼしい","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "乗", "answers": [ "ジョウ","のせる","のる","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "乙", "answers": [ "オツ","イツ","おと","きのと" ]},
		{ "question": "九", "answers": [ "キュウ","ク","ここの","ここのつ","あまた" ]},
		{ "question": "乞", "answers": [ "こう","キ","キツ","コツ" ]},
		{ "question": "乱", "answers": [ "ラン","みだす","みだれる","ロン","みだりに" ]},
		{ "question": "乳", "answers": [ "ニュウ","ちち","ち","ジュ","ニュ" ]},
		{ "question": "乾", "answers": [ "カン","かわかす","かわく","ケン","いぬい","ひ","ほす" ]},
		{ "question": "亀", "answers": [ "キ","かめ","キュウ","キン","あかぎれ" ]},
		{ "question": "了", "answers": [ "リョウ","おわる","さとる","しまう" ]},
		{ "question": "予", "answers": [ "ヨ","あたえる","あらかじめ","かねて","ゆるす","われ" ]},
		{ "question": "争", "answers": [ "ソウ","あらそう","いさめる" ]},
		{ "question": "事", "answers": [ "ジ","こと","ズ","つかえる" ]},
		{ "question": "二", "answers": [ "ニ","ふた","ふたつ","ジ" ]},
		{ "question": "互", "answers": [ "ゴ","たがい","かたみに" ]},
		{ "question": "五", "answers": [ "ゴ","いつ","いつつ" ]},
		{ "question": "井", "answers": [ "ショウ","い","セイ","いげた" ]},
		{ "question": "亜", "answers": [ "ア","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "亡", "answers": [ "ボウ","モウ","ない","ブ","ム","うしなう","にげる","ほろびる","ほろぼす" ]},
		{ "question": "交", "answers": [ "コウ","まざる","まじえる","まじる","まじわる","まぜる","かう","かわす","こもごも" ]},
		{ "question": "享", "answers": [ "キョウ","あたる","うける","すすめる" ]},
		{ "question": "京", "answers": [ "キョウ","ケイ","キン","みやこ" ]},
		{ "question": "亭", "answers": [ "テイ","チン","あずまや","とどまる" ]},
		{ "question": "人", "answers": [ "ジン","ニン","ひと" ]},
		{ "question": "仁", "answers": [ "ジン","ニ","ニン" ]},
		{ "question": "今", "answers": [ "コン","いま","キン" ]},
		{ "question": "介", "answers": [ "カイ","すけ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "仏", "answers": [ "ブツ","ほとけ","フツ" ]},
		{ "question": "仕", "answers": [ "シ","つかえる","ジ","つかまつる" ]},
		{ "question": "他", "answers": [ "タ","ほか" ]},
		{ "question": "付", "answers": [ "フ","つく","つける","あたえる" ]},
		{ "question": "仙", "answers": [ "セン" ]},
		{ "question": "代", "answers": [ "タイ","ダイ","かえる","かわる","よ","しろ" ]},
		{ "question": "令", "answers": [ "レイ","リョウ","いいつけ","おさ","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "以", "answers": [ "イ","もちいる","もって" ]},
		{ "question": "仮", "answers": [ "カ","かり","ケ","カク","かす" ]},
		{ "question": "仰", "answers": [ "ギョウ","コウ","あおぐ","おおせ","ゴウ","あおのく","のく" ]},
		{ "question": "仲", "answers": [ "なか","チュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "件", "answers": [ "ケン","くだり","くだん" ]},
		{ "question": "任", "answers": [ "ニン","まかす","まかせる","ジン" ]},
		{ "question": "企", "answers": [ "キ","くわだてる","たくらむ" ]},
		{ "question": "伎", "answers": [ "キ","ギ","たくみ","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "伏", "answers": [ "フク","ふす","ふせる","ブク","かくれる","したがう" ]},
		{ "question": "伐", "answers": [ "バツ","ハツ","うつ","きる","ほこる" ]},
		{ "question": "休", "answers": [ "キュウ","やすまる","やすむ","やすめる","ク","いこう","さいわい","やめる","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "会", "answers": [ "カイ","あう","エ","あつまる","あつめる" ]},
		{ "question": "伝", "answers": [ "デン","つたう","つたえる","つたわる","テン","つて" ]},
		{ "question": "伯", "answers": [ "ハク","ハ","おさ","かしら","はたがしら" ]},
		{ "question": "伴", "answers": [ "ハン","バン","ともなう","とも" ]},
		{ "question": "伸", "answers": [ "シン","のばす","のびる","のべる","のす","のる" ]},
		{ "question": "伺", "answers": [ "うかがう","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "似", "answers": [ "にる","ジ","シ","ごとし" ]},
		{ "question": "但", "answers": [ "ただし","タン","ダン","ただ" ]},
		{ "question": "位", "answers": [ "イ","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "低", "answers": [ "テイ","ひくい","ひくまる","ひくめる","たれる" ]},
		{ "question": "住", "answers": [ "ジュウ","すまう","すむ","チュウ","とどまる" ]},
		{ "question": "佐", "answers": [ "サ","すけ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "体", "answers": [ "タイ","からだ","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "何", "answers": [ "なに","なん","カ","いずく","いずれ" ]},
		{ "question": "余", "answers": [ "ヨ","あます","あまる","ほか","われ" ]},
		{ "question": "作", "answers": [ "サ","サク","つくる","なす" ]},
		{ "question": "佳", "answers": [ "カ","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "併", "answers": [ "ヘイ","あわせる","しかし","ならぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "使", "answers": [ "シ","つかう","つかわす" ]},
		{ "question": "例", "answers": [ "レイ","たとえる","たぐい","たとえば","ためし" ]},
		{ "question": "侍", "answers": [ "ジ","さむらい","シ","さぶらう","はべる" ]},
		{ "question": "供", "answers": [ "キョウ","そなえる","とも","ク" ]},
		{ "question": "依", "answers": [ "イ","エ","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "価", "answers": [ "カ","あたい" ]},
		{ "question": "侮", "answers": [ "ブ","あなどる" ]},
		{ "question": "侯", "answers": [ "コウ","きみ","まと" ]},
		{ "question": "侵", "answers": [ "シン","おかす","みにくい" ]},
		{ "question": "侶", "answers": [ "リョ","ロ","とも" ]},
		{ "question": "便", "answers": [ "ビン","ベン","たより","ヘン","いばり","すなわち","へつらう","よすが" ]},
		{ "question": "係", "answers": [ "ケイ","かかり","かかる","かかわる","つなぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "促", "answers": [ "ソク","うながす","せまる" ]},
		{ "question": "俊", "answers": [ "シュン","すぐれる" ]},
		{ "question": "俗", "answers": [ "ゾク","いやしい","ならわし" ]},
		{ "question": "保", "answers": [ "ホ","たもつ","ホウ","もつ","やすんじる" ]},
		{ "question": "信", "answers": [ "シン","たより","まかせる","まこと" ]},
		{ "question": "修", "answers": [ "シュウ","おさまる","おさめる","シュ","かざる","ながい" ]},
		{ "question": "俳", "answers": [ "ハイ","たわむれ","わざおぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "俵", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","たわら" ]},
		{ "question": "俸", "answers": [ "ホウ","ふち" ]},
		{ "question": "俺", "answers": [ "おれ","エン","われ" ]},
		{ "question": "倉", "answers": [ "ソウ","くら","にわか" ]},
		{ "question": "個", "answers": [ "コ","カ" ]},
		{ "question": "倍", "answers": [ "バイ","ハイ","そむく","ます" ]},
		{ "question": "倒", "answers": [ "トウ","たおす","たおれる","こける","さかさま" ]},
		{ "question": "候", "answers": [ "コウ","そうろう","うかがう","さぶらう","まつ" ]},
		{ "question": "借", "answers": [ "シャク","かりる","シャ" ]},
		{ "question": "倣", "answers": [ "ホウ","ならう" ]},
		{ "question": "値", "answers": [ "チ","ね","あたい","チョク","あう" ]},
		{ "question": "倫", "answers": [ "リン","たぐい","ついで","みち" ]},
		{ "question": "倹", "answers": [ "ケン","つづまやか","つましい" ]},
		{ "question": "偉", "answers": [ "イ","えらい","すぐれる" ]},
		{ "question": "偏", "answers": [ "ヘン","かたよる","ひとえに" ]},
		{ "question": "停", "answers": [ "テイ","とどまる","とまる" ]},
		{ "question": "健", "answers": [ "ケン","すこやか","したたか","たけし" ]},
		{ "question": "側", "answers": [ "ソク","がわ","ショク","かたわら","かわ","そば","はた" ]},
		{ "question": "偵", "answers": [ "テイ","うかがう" ]},
		{ "question": "偶", "answers": [ "グウ","たぐい","たまたま","ひとがた" ]},
		{ "question": "偽", "answers": [ "ギ","いつわる","にせ" ]},
		{ "question": "傍", "answers": [ "ボウ","かたわら","ホウ","そう","そば","はた","わき" ]},
		{ "question": "傑", "answers": [ "ケツ","すぐれる" ]},
		{ "question": "傘", "answers": [ "かさ","サン" ]},
		{ "question": "備", "answers": [ "ビ","そなえる","そなわる","ヒ","つぶさに" ]},
		{ "question": "催", "answers": [ "サイ","もよおす","うながす","もよい" ]},
		{ "question": "傲", "answers": [ "ゴウ","あそぶ","あなどる","おごる" ]},
		{ "question": "債", "answers": [ "サイ","かし","かり" ]},
		{ "question": "傷", "answers": [ "ショウ","きず","いたむ","いためる","そこなう" ]},
		{ "question": "傾", "answers": [ "ケイ","かたむく","かたむける","かしぐ","かたげる","くつがえる" ]},
		{ "question": "僅", "answers": [ "キン","わずか","わずかに" ]},
		{ "question": "働", "answers": [ "ドウ","はたらく" ]},
		{ "question": "像", "answers": [ "ゾウ","ショウ","かたち","かたどる" ]},
		{ "question": "僕", "answers": [ "ボク","ホク","しもべ","やつがれ" ]},
		{ "question": "僚", "answers": [ "リョウ","つかさ","とも" ]},
		{ "question": "僧", "answers": [ "ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "儀", "answers": [ "ギ","のり","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "億", "answers": [ "オク","おしはかる" ]},
		{ "question": "儒", "answers": [ "ジュ" ]},
		{ "question": "償", "answers": [ "ショウ","つぐなう" ]},
		{ "question": "優", "answers": [ "ユウ","すぐれる","やさしい","ウ","まさる","やわらぐ","ゆたか","わざおぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "元", "answers": [ "ガン","ゲン","もと","はじめ" ]},
		{ "question": "兄", "answers": [ "キョウ","あに","ケイ","え" ]},
		{ "question": "充", "answers": [ "ジュウ","あてる","シュウ","みたす","みちる","みつ" ]},
		{ "question": "兆", "answers": [ "チョウ","きざし","きざす","ジョウ","うらない" ]},
		{ "question": "先", "answers": [ "セン","さき","まず" ]},
		{ "question": "光", "answers": [ "コウ","ひかり","ひかる" ]},
		{ "question": "克", "answers": [ "コク","かつ","よく" ]},
		{ "question": "免", "answers": [ "メン","まぬかれる","ブン","ベン","うむ","やめる","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "児", "answers": [ "ジ","ニ","こ" ]},
		{ "question": "党", "answers": [ "トウ","なかま","むら" ]},
		{ "question": "入", "answers": [ "ニュウ","いる","いれる","はいる","ジュ","ジュウ","しお" ]},
		{ "question": "全", "answers": [ "ゼン","すべて","まったく","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "八", "answers": [ "ハチ","や","やつ","やっつ","よう" ]},
		{ "question": "公", "answers": [ "コウ","おおやけ","ク","きみ" ]},
		{ "question": "六", "answers": [ "ロク","む","むい","むつ","むっつ","リク" ]},
		{ "question": "共", "answers": [ "キョウ","とも" ]},
		{ "question": "兵", "answers": [ "ヘイ","ヒョウ","いくさ","つわもの" ]},
		{ "question": "具", "answers": [ "グ","つぶさに","つま","そなえる","そなわる" ]},
		{ "question": "典", "answers": [ "テン","のり","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "兼", "answers": [ "ケン","かねる","あわせる" ]},
		{ "question": "内", "answers": [ "ナイ","うち","ダイ","ドウ","ノウ","いる","いれる" ]},
		{ "question": "円", "answers": [ "エン","まるい","つぶらか","まどか","まろやか" ]},
		{ "question": "冊", "answers": [ "サツ","サク","たてる","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "再", "answers": [ "サ","サイ","ふたたび" ]},
		{ "question": "冒", "answers": [ "ボウ","おかす","ボク","モウ","おおう","ねたむ","むさぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "冗", "answers": [ "ジョウ","むだ" ]},
		{ "question": "写", "answers": [ "シャ","うつす","うつる" ]},
		{ "question": "冠", "answers": [ "カン","かんむり","かむる" ]},
		{ "question": "冥", "answers": [ "メイ","ミョウ","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "冬", "answers": [ "トウ","ふゆ" ]},
		{ "question": "冶", "answers": [ "ヤ","いる","とける","なまめかしい" ]},
		{ "question": "冷", "answers": [ "レイ","さます","さめる","つめたい","ひえる","ひや","ひやかす","ひやす" ]},
		{ "question": "凄", "answers": [ "セイ","さむい","すごい","すごむ","すさまじい" ]},
		{ "question": "准", "answers": [ "ジュン","シュン","なぞらえる","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "凍", "answers": [ "トウ","こおる","こごえる","いてる","しみる" ]},
		{ "question": "凝", "answers": [ "ギョウ","こらす","こる","こごる","しこり" ]},
		{ "question": "凡", "answers": [ "ボン","ハン","およそ","すべて","なみ" ]},
		{ "question": "処", "answers": [ "ショ","ソ","おく","おる","ところ" ]},
		{ "question": "凶", "answers": [ "キョウ","おそれる","わざわい","わるい" ]},
		{ "question": "凸", "answers": [ "トツ","でこ" ]},
		{ "question": "凹", "answers": [ "オウ","くぼむ","へこます","へこむ" ]},
		{ "question": "出", "answers": [ "シュツ","だす","でる","スイ","いだす","いづ" ]},
		{ "question": "刀", "answers": [ "トウ","かたな" ]},
		{ "question": "刃", "answers": [ "は","ジン","ニン","きる","やいば" ]},
		{ "question": "分", "answers": [ "ブ","フン","ブン","わかつ","わかる","わかれる","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "切", "answers": [ "セツ","きる","きれる","サイ" ]},
		{ "question": "刈", "answers": [ "かる","カイ","ガイ" ]},
		{ "question": "刊", "answers": [ "カン","きざむ","けずる" ]},
		{ "question": "刑", "answers": [ "ケイ","ギョウ","しおき","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "列", "answers": [ "レツ","つらなる","つらねる","ならべる" ]},
		{ "question": "初", "answers": [ "ショ","はじめ","はじめて","はつ","そめる","うい","ソ","うぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "判", "answers": [ "ハン","バン","ホウ","わかる","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "別", "answers": [ "ベツ","わかれる","ベチ","わかつ","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "利", "answers": [ "リ","きく","するどい","とし","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "到", "answers": [ "トウ","いたる" ]},
		{ "question": "制", "answers": [ "セイ","おさえる" ]},
		{ "question": "刷", "answers": [ "サツ","する","はく" ]},
		{ "question": "券", "answers": [ "ケン","てがた","わりふ" ]},
		{ "question": "刹", "answers": [ "セツ","サツ","てら" ]},
		{ "question": "刺", "answers": [ "シ","ささる","さす","セキ","そしる","とげ","なふだ" ]},
		{ "question": "刻", "answers": [ "コク","きざむ","とき" ]},
		{ "question": "則", "answers": [ "ソク","すなわち","のっとる","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "削", "answers": [ "サク","けずる","ショウ","そぐ","はつる" ]},
		{ "question": "前", "answers": [ "ゼン","まえ","セン","さき" ]},
		{ "question": "剖", "answers": [ "ボウ","ホウ","さく","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "剛", "answers": [ "ゴウ","コウ","かたい","つよい" ]},
		{ "question": "剝", "answers": [ "ハク","はがす","はがれる","はぐ","はげる","ホク","とる","むく" ]},
		{ "question": "剣", "answers": [ "ケン","つるぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "剤", "answers": [ "ザイ","スイ","セイ","まぜる" ]},
		{ "question": "副", "answers": [ "フク","フウ","そう" ]},
		{ "question": "剰", "answers": [ "ジョウ","あます","あまつさえ","あまる" ]},
		{ "question": "割", "answers": [ "わり","わる","われる","カツ","さく" ]},
		{ "question": "創", "answers": [ "ソウ","つくる","きず","はじめる" ]},
		{ "question": "劇", "answers": [ "ゲキ","はげしい" ]},
		{ "question": "力", "answers": [ "リキ","リョク","ちから","つとめる","りきむ" ]},
		{ "question": "功", "answers": [ "コウ","ク","いさお" ]},
		{ "question": "加", "answers": [ "カ","くわえる","くわわる" ]},
		{ "question": "劣", "answers": [ "レツ","おとる","いやしい" ]},
		{ "question": "助", "answers": [ "ジョ","たすかる","たすける","すけ" ]},
		{ "question": "努", "answers": [ "ド","つとめる","ゆめ" ]},
		{ "question": "励", "answers": [ "レイ","はげます","はげむ" ]},
		{ "question": "労", "answers": [ "ロウ","いたわる","つかれる","ねぎらう","はたらく" ]},
		{ "question": "効", "answers": [ "コウ","きく","いたす","かい","ならう" ]},
		{ "question": "劾", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","あばく","しらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "勃", "answers": [ "ボツ","ホツ","おこる","にわかに" ]},
		{ "question": "勅", "answers": [ "チョク","いましめる","みことのり" ]},
		{ "question": "勇", "answers": [ "ユウ","いさむ","ヨウ","いさましい","つよい" ]},
		{ "question": "勉", "answers": [ "ベン","つとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "動", "answers": [ "ドウ","うごかす","うごく","トウ","ややもすれば" ]},
		{ "question": "勘", "answers": [ "カン","かんがえる" ]},
		{ "question": "務", "answers": [ "ム","つとまる","つとめる","ブ","あなどり","あなどる","つとめ" ]},
		{ "question": "勝", "answers": [ "ショウ","かつ","まさる","すぐれる","たえる" ]},
		{ "question": "募", "answers": [ "ボ","つのる","モ" ]},
		{ "question": "勢", "answers": [ "セイ","いきおい","セ" ]},
		{ "question": "勤", "answers": [ "キン","つとまる","つとめる","ゴン","いそしむ","つとめ" ]},
		{ "question": "勧", "answers": [ "カン","すすめる","ケン" ]},
		{ "question": "勲", "answers": [ "クン","いさお","いさおし" ]},
		{ "question": "勾", "answers": [ "コウ","とらえる","まがる" ]},
		{ "question": "匂", "answers": [ "におう" ]},
		{ "question": "包", "answers": [ "ホウ","つつむ","くるむ" ]},
		{ "question": "化", "answers": [ "カ","ばかす","ばける","ケ","かえる","かわる" ]},
		{ "question": "北", "answers": [ "ホク","きた","ハイ","そむく","にげる" ]},
		{ "question": "匠", "answers": [ "ショウ","たくみ" ]},
		{ "question": "匹", "answers": [ "ヒツ","ひき","ヒキ","たぐう" ]},
		{ "question": "区", "answers": [ "ク","オウ" ]},
		{ "question": "医", "answers": [ "イ","いやす","くすし" ]},
		{ "question": "匿", "answers": [ "トク","ジョク","かくまう","かくれる" ]},
		{ "question": "十", "answers": [ "ジッ","ジュウ","と","とお","ジュッ" ]},
		{ "question": "千", "answers": [ "セン","ち" ]},
		{ "question": "升", "answers": [ "ショウ","ます","のぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "午", "answers": [ "ゴ","うま","ひる" ]},
		{ "question": "半", "answers": [ "ハン","なかば" ]},
		{ "question": "卑", "answers": [ "ヒ","いやしい","いやしむ","いやしめる","ひくい" ]},
		{ "question": "卒", "answers": [ "ソツ","シュツ","おえる","おわる","しもべ","ついに","にわかに" ]},
		{ "question": "卓", "answers": [ "タク","シツ","すぐれる","つくえ" ]},
		{ "question": "協", "answers": [ "キョウ","かなう" ]},
		{ "question": "南", "answers": [ "ナン","みなみ","ナ","ダン" ]},
		{ "question": "単", "answers": [ "タン","ゼン","ひとえ","ひとつ" ]},
		{ "question": "博", "answers": [ "ハク","バク","ひろい","ひろめる" ]},
		{ "question": "占", "answers": [ "セン","うらなう","しめる" ]},
		{ "question": "印", "answers": [ "イン","しるし","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "危", "answers": [ "キ","あぶない","あやうい","あやぶむ","あやめる","たかい" ]},
		{ "question": "即", "answers": [ "ソク","ショク","すなわち","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "却", "answers": [ "キャク","かえって","しりぞく","しりぞける" ]},
		{ "question": "卵", "answers": [ "たまご","ラン" ]},
		{ "question": "卸", "answers": [ "おろし","おろす","シャ" ]},
		{ "question": "厄", "answers": [ "ヤク","アク","くるしむ","わざわい" ]},
		{ "question": "厘", "answers": [ "リン","テン","デン","リ" ]},
		{ "question": "厚", "answers": [ "あつい","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "原", "answers": [ "ゲン","はら","たずねる","もと","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "厳", "answers": [ "ゲン","きびしい","おごそか","ゴン","いかつい","いかめしい" ]},
		{ "question": "去", "answers": [ "キョ","コ","さる","のぞく","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "参", "answers": [ "サン","まいる","シン","まじわる" ]},
		{ "question": "又", "answers": [ "また","ウ","ユウ","ふたたび" ]},
		{ "question": "及", "answers": [ "キュウ","および","およぶ","およぼす" ]},
		{ "question": "友", "answers": [ "ユウ","とも","ウ" ]},
		{ "question": "双", "answers": [ "ソウ","ふた","たぐい","ならぶ","ふたつ","もろ" ]},
		{ "question": "反", "answers": [ "ハン","そらす","そる","タン","ホン","かえす","かえる","そむく" ]},
		{ "question": "収", "answers": [ "シュウ","おさまる","おさめる" ]},
		{ "question": "叔", "answers": [ "シュク","わかい" ]},
		{ "question": "取", "answers": [ "シュ","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "受", "answers": [ "ジュ","うかる","うける","ズ" ]},
		{ "question": "叙", "answers": [ "ジョ","のべる" ]},
		{ "question": "口", "answers": [ "ク","コウ","くち" ]},
		{ "question": "古", "answers": [ "コ","ふるい","ふるす","いにしえ" ]},
		{ "question": "句", "answers": [ "ク","コウ","あたる","まがる" ]},
		{ "question": "叫", "answers": [ "キョウ","さけぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "召", "answers": [ "ショウ","めす" ]},
		{ "question": "可", "answers": [ "カ","コク","べし","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "台", "answers": [ "タイ","ダイ","イ","うてな","しもべ" ]},
		{ "question": "叱", "answers": [ "シツ","しかる","シチ" ]},
		{ "question": "史", "answers": [ "シ","ふびと","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "右", "answers": [ "ウ","ユウ","みぎ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "号", "answers": [ "ゴウ","コウ","さけぶ","よびな" ]},
		{ "question": "司", "answers": [ "シ","ス","つかさ","つかさどる" ]},
		{ "question": "各", "answers": [ "カク","おのおの" ]},
		{ "question": "合", "answers": [ "カッ","ガッ","ゴウ","あう","あわす","あわせる","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "吉", "answers": [ "キチ","キツ","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "同", "answers": [ "ドウ","おなじ","トウ","ともに" ]},
		{ "question": "名", "answers": [ "ミョウ","メイ","な" ]},
		{ "question": "后", "answers": [ "コウ","ゴ","きさき","きみ","のち" ]},
		{ "question": "吏", "answers": [ "リ","つかさ" ]},
		{ "question": "吐", "answers": [ "ト","はく","つく","ぬかす" ]},
		{ "question": "向", "answers": [ "コウ","むかう","むく","むける","むこう","キョウ","ショウ","さきに" ]},
		{ "question": "君", "answers": [ "クン","きみ" ]},
		{ "question": "吟", "answers": [ "ギン","うたう","うめく" ]},
		{ "question": "否", "answers": [ "ヒ","いな","フ","いや","わるい" ]},
		{ "question": "含", "answers": [ "ガン","ふくむ","ふくめる","カン","ゴン" ]},
		{ "question": "吸", "answers": [ "キュウ","すう" ]},
		{ "question": "吹", "answers": [ "スイ","ふく" ]},
		{ "question": "呂", "answers": [ "ロ","リョ" ]},
		{ "question": "呈", "answers": [ "テイ","しめす" ]},
		{ "question": "呉", "answers": [ "ゴ","くれ","くれる" ]},
		{ "question": "告", "answers": [ "コク","つげる","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "周", "answers": [ "シュウ","まわり","ス","あまねく","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "呪", "answers": [ "ジュ","のろう","シュ","シュウ","まじない","まじなう" ]},
		{ "question": "味", "answers": [ "ミ","あじ","あじわう","ビ" ]},
		{ "question": "呼", "answers": [ "コ","よぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "命", "answers": [ "メイ","いのち","ミョウ","おおせ","みこと" ]},
		{ "question": "和", "answers": [ "ワ","なごむ","なごやか","やわらぐ","やわらげる","オ","カ","あえる","なぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "咲", "answers": [ "さく","ショウ","わらう" ]},
		{ "question": "咽", "answers": [ "イン","エツ","エン","のど","のむ","むせぶ","むせる" ]},
		{ "question": "哀", "answers": [ "アイ","あわれ","あわれむ","かなしい","かなしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "品", "answers": [ "ヒン","しな","ホン" ]},
		{ "question": "員", "answers": [ "イン","エン","ウン","かず" ]},
		{ "question": "哲", "answers": [ "テツ","あきらか","さとい" ]},
		{ "question": "哺", "answers": [ "ホ","はぐくむ","ふくむ" ]},
		{ "question": "唄", "answers": [ "うた","ハイ","バイ","うたう" ]},
		{ "question": "唆", "answers": [ "サ","そそのかす" ]},
		{ "question": "唇", "answers": [ "くちびる","シン" ]},
		{ "question": "唐", "answers": [ "トウ","から","もろこし" ]},
		{ "question": "唯", "answers": [ "ユイ","イ","ただ" ]},
		{ "question": "唱", "answers": [ "ショウ","となえる","うた","うたう" ]},
		{ "question": "唾", "answers": [ "ダ","つば","タ","つばき" ]},
		{ "question": "商", "answers": [ "ショウ","あきなう","あきない","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "問", "answers": [ "モン","とい","とう","とん","ブン","たずねる","たより" ]},
		{ "question": "啓", "answers": [ "ケイ","ひらく","もうす" ]},
		{ "question": "善", "answers": [ "ゼン","よい","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "喉", "answers": [ "コウ","のど" ]},
		{ "question": "喚", "answers": [ "カン","さけぶ","よぶ","わめく" ]},
		{ "question": "喜", "answers": [ "キ","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "喝", "answers": [ "カツ","おどす","しかる" ]},
		{ "question": "喩", "answers": [ "ユ","さとす","たとえる","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "喪", "answers": [ "ソウ","も","うしなう","ほろびる","ほろぼす" ]},
		{ "question": "喫", "answers": [ "キツ","くう","すう","のむ" ]},
		{ "question": "営", "answers": [ "エイ","いとなむ","ヨウ" ]},
		{ "question": "嗅", "answers": [ "キュウ","かぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "嗣", "answers": [ "シ","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "嘆", "answers": [ "タン","なげかわしい","なげく" ]},
		{ "question": "嘱", "answers": [ "ショク","たのむ" ]},
		{ "question": "嘲", "answers": [ "チョウ","あざける","トウ","からかう" ]},
		{ "question": "器", "answers": [ "キ","うつわ" ]},
		{ "question": "噴", "answers": [ "フン","ふく","ホン","はく" ]},
		{ "question": "嚇", "answers": [ "カク","いかる","おどかす","おどす" ]},
		{ "question": "囚", "answers": [ "シュウ","とらえる","とらわれる" ]},
		{ "question": "四", "answers": [ "シ","よ","よつ","よっつ","よん" ]},
		{ "question": "回", "answers": [ "カイ","まわす","まわる","エ","めぐらす","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "因", "answers": [ "イン","よる","ちなみ","ちなむ","よすが","よって" ]},
		{ "question": "団", "answers": [ "ダン","トン","タン","かたまり","まるい" ]},
		{ "question": "困", "answers": [ "コン","こまる","くるしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "囲", "answers": [ "イ","かこう","かこむ" ]},
		{ "question": "図", "answers": [ "ズ","ト","はかる","え" ]},
		{ "question": "固", "answers": [ "コ","かたい","かたまる","かためる","もとより" ]},
		{ "question": "国", "answers": [ "コク","くに" ]},
		{ "question": "圏", "answers": [ "ケン","かこい" ]},
		{ "question": "園", "answers": [ "エン","その","オン","にわ" ]},
		{ "question": "土", "answers": [ "ト","ド","つち" ]},
		{ "question": "圧", "answers": [ "アツ","オウ","おさえる","おす","へす" ]},
		{ "question": "在", "answers": [ "ザイ","ある","います","まします" ]},
		{ "question": "地", "answers": [ "ジ","チ","つち","ところ" ]},
		{ "question": "坂", "answers": [ "さか","ハン","バン" ]},
		{ "question": "均", "answers": [ "キン","イン","ウン","ととのえる","ならす","ひとしい" ]},
		{ "question": "坊", "answers": [ "ボウ","ボッ","ホウ","へや","まち" ]},
		{ "question": "坑", "answers": [ "コウ","あな" ]},
		{ "question": "坪", "answers": [ "つぼ","ヘイ" ]},
		{ "question": "垂", "answers": [ "スイ","たらす","たれる","しだれる","しで","なんなんとする" ]},
		{ "question": "型", "answers": [ "ケイ","かた" ]},
		{ "question": "垣", "answers": [ "かき","エン" ]},
		{ "question": "埋", "answers": [ "マイ","うまる","うめる","うもれる","いける","うずまる","うずもれる" ]},
		{ "question": "城", "answers": [ "ジョウ","しろ","セイ","き" ]},
		{ "question": "域", "answers": [ "イキ","ヨク","さかい","ところ" ]},
		{ "question": "執", "answers": [ "シツ","シュウ","とる","とらえる" ]},
		{ "question": "培", "answers": [ "バイ","つちかう","ハイ","ホウ","おか" ]},
		{ "question": "基", "answers": [ "キ","もと","もとい","もとづく" ]},
		{ "question": "埼", "answers": [ "さい","キ","さき" ]},
		{ "question": "堀", "answers": [ "ほり","クツ","コツ","あな" ]},
		{ "question": "堂", "answers": [ "ドウ","トウ","たかどの" ]},
		{ "question": "堅", "answers": [ "ケン","かたい" ]},
		{ "question": "堆", "answers": [ "タイ","ツイ","うずたかい" ]},
		{ "question": "堕", "answers": [ "ダ","キ","おちる","おとす","おろす","こぼつ" ]},
		{ "question": "堤", "answers": [ "テイ","つつみ" ]},
		{ "question": "堪", "answers": [ "たえる","カン","タン","こたえる","こらえる","たまる" ]},
		{ "question": "報", "answers": [ "ホウ","むくいる","しらせる" ]},
		{ "question": "場", "answers": [ "ジョウ","ば" ]},
		{ "question": "塀", "answers": [ "ヘイ" ]},
		{ "question": "塁", "answers": [ "ルイ","かさねる","とりで" ]},
		{ "question": "塊", "answers": [ "カイ","かたまり","つちくれ" ]},
		{ "question": "塑", "answers": [ "ソ","でく" ]},
		{ "question": "塔", "answers": [ "トウ" ]},
		{ "question": "塗", "answers": [ "ト","ぬる","どろ","まぶす","まみれる","みち" ]},
		{ "question": "塚", "answers": [ "つか","チョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "塞", "answers": [ "サイ","ソク","ふさがる","ふさぐ","せく","とりで","みちる" ]},
		{ "question": "塡", "answers": [ "テン","チン","うずまる","うずめる","はまる","はめる","ふさがる","ふさぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "塩", "answers": [ "エン","しお","アン" ]},
		{ "question": "塾", "answers": [ "ジュク" ]},
		{ "question": "境", "answers": [ "キョウ","さかい","ケイ" ]},
		{ "question": "墓", "answers": [ "ボ","はか" ]},
		{ "question": "増", "answers": [ "ゾウ","ふえる","ふやす","ます","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "墜", "answers": [ "ツイ","おちる","おとす" ]},
		{ "question": "墨", "answers": [ "ボク","すみ","モク" ]},
		{ "question": "墳", "answers": [ "フン","はか" ]},
		{ "question": "墾", "answers": [ "コン","ひらく" ]},
		{ "question": "壁", "answers": [ "ヘキ","かべ","がけ" ]},
		{ "question": "壇", "answers": [ "ダン","タン" ]},
		{ "question": "壊", "answers": [ "カイ","こわす","こわれる","エ","やぶる","やぶれる" ]},
		{ "question": "壌", "answers": [ "ジョウ","つち" ]},
		{ "question": "士", "answers": [ "シ","さむらい" ]},
		{ "question": "壮", "answers": [ "ソウ","さかん" ]},
		{ "question": "声", "answers": [ "セイ","こえ","こわ","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "壱", "answers": [ "イチ","イツ","ひとつ" ]},
		{ "question": "売", "answers": [ "バイ","うる","うれる" ]},
		{ "question": "変", "answers": [ "ヘン","かえる","かわる" ]},
		{ "question": "夏", "answers": [ "カ","なつ","ゲ" ]},
		{ "question": "夕", "answers": [ "ゆう","セキ","ゆうべ" ]},
		{ "question": "外", "answers": [ "ガイ","そと","はずす","はずれる","ほか","ゲ","ウイ","と" ]},
		{ "question": "多", "answers": [ "タ","おおい" ]},
		{ "question": "夜", "answers": [ "ヤ","よ","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "夢", "answers": [ "ム","ゆめ","ボウ" ]},
		{ "question": "大", "answers": [ "タイ","ダイ","おお","おおいに","おおきい","タ","ダ" ]},
		{ "question": "天", "answers": [ "テン","あま","あめ","そら" ]},
		{ "question": "太", "answers": [ "タ","タイ","ふとい","ふとる","ダイ","はなはだ" ]},
		{ "question": "夫", "answers": [ "フ","おっと","フウ","ブ","おとこ","それ" ]},
		{ "question": "央", "answers": [ "オウ","エイ","ヨウ","なかば" ]},
		{ "question": "失", "answers": [ "シツ","うしなう","イツ","うせる" ]},
		{ "question": "奇", "answers": [ "キ","あやしい","くし","めずらしい" ]},
		{ "question": "奈", "answers": [ "ナ","ダイ","ナイ","いかん","いかんぞ","なんぞ" ]},
		{ "question": "奉", "answers": [ "ブ","ホウ","たてまつる","うけたまわる","まつる" ]},
		{ "question": "奏", "answers": [ "ソウ","かなでる","すすめる" ]},
		{ "question": "契", "answers": [ "ケイ","ちぎる","キツ","ケツ","セツ","きざむ","ちぎり","わりふ" ]},
		{ "question": "奔", "answers": [ "ホン","はしる" ]},
		{ "question": "奥", "answers": [ "おく","オウ","イク","くま" ]},
		{ "question": "奨", "answers": [ "ショウ","ソウ","すすめる" ]},
		{ "question": "奪", "answers": [ "ダツ","うばう","タツ" ]},
		{ "question": "奮", "answers": [ "フン","ふるう" ]},
		{ "question": "女", "answers": [ "ジョ","おんな","ニョ","め","ニョウ","なんじ","むすめ","めあわせる" ]},
		{ "question": "奴", "answers": [ "ド","ヌ","め","やつ","やっこ" ]},
		{ "question": "好", "answers": [ "コウ","このむ","すく","よい","よしみ" ]},
		{ "question": "如", "answers": [ "ジョ","ニョ","ごとし","しく","もし","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "妃", "answers": [ "ヒ","ハイ","きさき" ]},
		{ "question": "妄", "answers": [ "モウ","ボウ","みだりに" ]},
		{ "question": "妊", "answers": [ "ニン","ジン","はらむ","みごもる" ]},
		{ "question": "妖", "answers": [ "ヨウ","あやしい","なまめかしい","わざわい" ]},
		{ "question": "妙", "answers": [ "ミョウ","ビョウ","たえ","わかい" ]},
		{ "question": "妥", "answers": [ "ダ","タ","おだやか","やすらか" ]},
		{ "question": "妨", "answers": [ "ボウ","さまたげる","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "妬", "answers": [ "ト","ねたむ","そねむ","やく" ]},
		{ "question": "妹", "answers": [ "いもうと","マイ","バイ","いも" ]},
		{ "question": "妻", "answers": [ "サイ","つま","セイ","めあわす" ]},
		{ "question": "姉", "answers": [ "あね","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "始", "answers": [ "シ","はじまる","はじめる" ]},
		{ "question": "姓", "answers": [ "ショウ","セイ","かばね" ]},
		{ "question": "委", "answers": [ "イ","ゆだねる","おく","くわしい","すてる","まかせる" ]},
		{ "question": "姫", "answers": [ "ひめ","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "姻", "answers": [ "イン","とつぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "姿", "answers": [ "シ","すがた" ]},
		{ "question": "威", "answers": [ "イ","おどす" ]},
		{ "question": "娘", "answers": [ "むすめ","ジョウ","ニョウ","こ" ]},
		{ "question": "娠", "answers": [ "シン","はらむ","みごもる" ]},
		{ "question": "娯", "answers": [ "ゴ","たのしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "婆", "answers": [ "バ","ばば" ]},
		{ "question": "婚", "answers": [ "コン" ]},
		{ "question": "婦", "answers": [ "フ","おんな" ]},
		{ "question": "婿", "answers": [ "むこ","セイ" ]},
		{ "question": "媒", "answers": [ "バイ","なかだち" ]},
		{ "question": "媛", "answers": [ "エン","ひめ" ]},
		{ "question": "嫁", "answers": [ "とつぐ","よめ","カ" ]},
		{ "question": "嫉", "answers": [ "シツ","そねむ","にくむ","ねたむ" ]},
		{ "question": "嫌", "answers": [ "ケン","ゲン","いや","きらう","うたがう" ]},
		{ "question": "嫡", "answers": [ "チャク","テキ","よつぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "嬢", "answers": [ "ジョウ","むすめ" ]},
		{ "question": "子", "answers": [ "シ","ス","こ","おとこ","ね","み" ]},
		{ "question": "孔", "answers": [ "コウ","ク","あな","はなはだ" ]},
		{ "question": "字", "answers": [ "ジ","あざ","シ","あざな" ]},
		{ "question": "存", "answers": [ "ソン","ゾン","ある","たもつ","とう","ながらえる" ]},
		{ "question": "孝", "answers": [ "コウ","キョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "季", "answers": [ "キ","すえ" ]},
		{ "question": "孤", "answers": [ "コ","そむく","ひとり","みなしご" ]},
		{ "question": "学", "answers": [ "ガク","まなぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "孫", "answers": [ "ソン","まご" ]},
		{ "question": "宅", "answers": [ "タク","いえ","やけ" ]},
		{ "question": "宇", "answers": [ "ウ","いえ","のき" ]},
		{ "question": "守", "answers": [ "シュ","ス","まもる","もり","かみ" ]},
		{ "question": "安", "answers": [ "アン","やすい","いずくんぞ","やすんじる" ]},
		{ "question": "完", "answers": [ "カン","まっとうする" ]},
		{ "question": "宗", "answers": [ "シュウ","ソウ","むね" ]},
		{ "question": "官", "answers": [ "カン","おおやけ","つかさ" ]},
		{ "question": "宙", "answers": [ "チュウ","そら" ]},
		{ "question": "定", "answers": [ "ジョウ","テイ","さだまる","さだめる","さだか","きまる" ]},
		{ "question": "宛", "answers": [ "あてる","エン","あたかも","あて","さながら","ずつ" ]},
		{ "question": "宜", "answers": [ "ギ","むべ","よい","よろしい","よろしく" ]},
		{ "question": "宝", "answers": [ "ホウ","たから" ]},
		{ "question": "実", "answers": [ "ジツ","み","みのる","さね","まこと","まめ","みちる" ]},
		{ "question": "客", "answers": [ "キャク","カク","まろうど" ]},
		{ "question": "宣", "answers": [ "セン","のたまう","のべる" ]},
		{ "question": "室", "answers": [ "シツ","むろ","いえ","つま","へや" ]},
		{ "question": "宮", "answers": [ "キュウ","みや","グウ","ク","いえ" ]},
		{ "question": "宰", "answers": [ "サイ","つかさどる" ]},
		{ "question": "害", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","カツ","そこなう","わざわい" ]},
		{ "question": "宴", "answers": [ "エン","うたげ","たのしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "宵", "answers": [ "よい","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "家", "answers": [ "カ","ケ","いえ","や","うち" ]},
		{ "question": "容", "answers": [ "ヨウ","いれる","かたち","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "宿", "answers": [ "シュク","やど","やどす","やどる","シュウ","スク" ]},
		{ "question": "寂", "answers": [ "ジャク","さび","さびしい","さびれる","セキ","さびる","しずか" ]},
		{ "question": "寄", "answers": [ "キ","よせる","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "密", "answers": [ "ミツ","ビツ","こまかい","ひそかに" ]},
		{ "question": "富", "answers": [ "フ","とみ","とむ","フウ" ]},
		{ "question": "寒", "answers": [ "カン","さむい","いやしい","さびしい","まずしい" ]},
		{ "question": "寛", "answers": [ "カン","くつろぐ","ひろい","ゆるやか" ]},
		{ "question": "寝", "answers": [ "シン","ねかす","ねる","みたまや","みにくい","やめる" ]},
		{ "question": "察", "answers": [ "サツ","あきらか","しる","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "寡", "answers": [ "カ","すくない","やもめ" ]},
		{ "question": "寧", "answers": [ "ネイ","デイ","ニョウ","いずくんぞ","なんぞ","ねんごろ","むしろ","やすい" ]},
		{ "question": "審", "answers": [ "シン","つまびらか" ]},
		{ "question": "寮", "answers": [ "リョウ","つかさ" ]},
		{ "question": "寸", "answers": [ "スン","ソン","き","わずか" ]},
		{ "question": "寺", "answers": [ "ジ","てら" ]},
		{ "question": "対", "answers": [ "タイ","ツイ","こたえる","そろい","つれあい","むかう" ]},
		{ "question": "寿", "answers": [ "ジュ","ことぶき","ス","いのちながし","ことほぐ","とし","ひさしい" ]},
		{ "question": "封", "answers": [ "フウ","ホウ","さかい","とじる","ポンド" ]},
		{ "question": "専", "answers": [ "セン","もっぱら","ほしいまま" ]},
		{ "question": "射", "answers": [ "シャ","いる","エキ","セキ","ヤ","あてる","うつ","さす" ]},
		{ "question": "将", "answers": [ "ショウ","はた","ひきいる","まさに" ]},
		{ "question": "尉", "answers": [ "イ","ウツ","じょう" ]},
		{ "question": "尊", "answers": [ "ソン","たっとい","たっとぶ","とうとい","とうとぶ","みこと" ]},
		{ "question": "尋", "answers": [ "ジン","たずねる","つね","ひろ" ]},
		{ "question": "導", "answers": [ "ドウ","みちびく","しるべ" ]},
		{ "question": "小", "answers": [ "ショウ","お","こ","ちいさい","さ" ]},
		{ "question": "少", "answers": [ "ショウ","すくない","すこし","しばらく","まれ","わかい" ]},
		{ "question": "尚", "answers": [ "ショウ","くわえる","たっとぶ","とうとぶ","なお" ]},
		{ "question": "就", "answers": [ "シュウ","つく","つける","ジュ","なす","なる" ]},
		{ "question": "尺", "answers": [ "シャク","セキ","さし","ものさし","わずか" ]},
		{ "question": "尻", "answers": [ "しり","コウ","けつ" ]},
		{ "question": "尼", "answers": [ "あま","ニ","ジ" ]},
		{ "question": "尽", "answers": [ "ジン","つかす","つきる","つくす","ことごとく","すがれる" ]},
		{ "question": "尾", "answers": [ "ビ","お" ]},
		{ "question": "尿", "answers": [ "ニョウ","いばり","しと","ゆばり" ]},
		{ "question": "局", "answers": [ "キョク","つぼね" ]},
		{ "question": "居", "answers": [ "キョ","いる","キ","コ","おく","おる" ]},
		{ "question": "屈", "answers": [ "クツ","かがむ","くぐまる","こごまる" ]},
		{ "question": "届", "answers": [ "とどく","とどける","カイ" ]},
		{ "question": "屋", "answers": [ "オク","や","いえ","やね" ]},
		{ "question": "展", "answers": [ "テン","つらねる","のべる","ひろげる" ]},
		{ "question": "属", "answers": [ "ゾク","ショク","つく","やから" ]},
		{ "question": "層", "answers": [ "ソウ","かさなる" ]},
		{ "question": "履", "answers": [ "リ","はく","くつ","ふむ" ]},
		{ "question": "屯", "answers": [ "トン","チュン","たむろ","なやむ" ]},
		{ "question": "山", "answers": [ "サン","やま","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "岐", "answers": [ "キ","ギ","ちまた","わかれる" ]},
		{ "question": "岡", "answers": [ "おか","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "岩", "answers": [ "ガン","いわ" ]},
		{ "question": "岬", "answers": [ "みさき","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "岳", "answers": [ "ガク","たけ" ]},
		{ "question": "岸", "answers": [ "ガン","きし","かどだつ" ]},
		{ "question": "峠", "answers": [ "とうげ" ]},
		{ "question": "峡", "answers": [ "キョウ","はざま" ]},
		{ "question": "峰", "answers": [ "ホウ","みね","フ" ]},
		{ "question": "島", "answers": [ "トウ","しま" ]},
		{ "question": "崇", "answers": [ "スウ","シュウ","あがめる","おわる","たかい","たっとぶ","とうとぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "崎", "answers": [ "さき","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "崖", "answers": [ "ガイ","がけ","かどだつ" ]},
		{ "question": "崩", "answers": [ "ホウ","くずす","くずれる" ]},
		{ "question": "嵐", "answers": [ "あらし","ラン" ]},
		{ "question": "川", "answers": [ "かわ","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "州", "answers": [ "シュウ","す","ス","くに","しま" ]},
		{ "question": "巡", "answers": [ "ジュン","めぐる","まわる" ]},
		{ "question": "巣", "answers": [ "す","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "工", "answers": [ "ク","コウ","たくみ","たくむ","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "左", "answers": [ "サ","ひだり" ]},
		{ "question": "巧", "answers": [ "コウ","たくみ","うまい","たくむ" ]},
		{ "question": "巨", "answers": [ "キョ","コ","おおい","おおきい" ]},
		{ "question": "差", "answers": [ "サ","さす","サイ","シ","たがう","つかわす" ]},
		{ "question": "己", "answers": [ "コ","キ","おのれ","つちのと" ]},
		{ "question": "巻", "answers": [ "カン","まき","まく","ケン" ]},
		{ "question": "巾", "answers": [ "キン","きれ","はば","ふきん" ]},
		{ "question": "市", "answers": [ "シ","いち" ]},
		{ "question": "布", "answers": [ "フ","ぬの","ホ","しく" ]},
		{ "question": "帆", "answers": [ "ハン","ほ" ]},
		{ "question": "希", "answers": [ "キ","ケ","こいねがう","まれ" ]},
		{ "question": "帝", "answers": [ "テイ","タイ","みかど" ]},
		{ "question": "帥", "answers": [ "スイ","ソツ","ひきいる" ]},
		{ "question": "師", "answers": [ "シ","いくさ","みやこ" ]},
		{ "question": "席", "answers": [ "セキ","むしろ" ]},
		{ "question": "帯", "answers": [ "タイ","おび","おびる" ]},
		{ "question": "帰", "answers": [ "キ","かえす","かえる","おくる","とつぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "帳", "answers": [ "チョウ","とばり","はり" ]},
		{ "question": "常", "answers": [ "ジョウ","つね","とこ" ]},
		{ "question": "帽", "answers": [ "ボウ" ]},
		{ "question": "幅", "answers": [ "フク","はば" ]},
		{ "question": "幕", "answers": [ "バク","マク" ]},
		{ "question": "幣", "answers": [ "ヘイ","ぜに","ぬさ","みてぐら" ]},
		{ "question": "干", "answers": [ "カン","ほす","ひる","おかす","かかわる","たて","もとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "平", "answers": [ "ビョウ","ヘイ","たいら","ヒョウ","ヘン" ]},
		{ "question": "年", "answers": [ "ネン","とし","デン","とせ","みのり","よわい" ]},
		{ "question": "幸", "answers": [ "コウ","さいわい","しあわせ","さち","みゆき" ]},
		{ "question": "幹", "answers": [ "カン","みき","から","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "幻", "answers": [ "ゲン","まぼろし","まどわす" ]},
		{ "question": "幼", "answers": [ "ヨウ","おさない","ユウ","いとけない" ]},
		{ "question": "幽", "answers": [ "ユウ","かすか","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "幾", "answers": [ "キ","いく","きざし","こいねがう","ほとんど" ]},
		{ "question": "庁", "answers": [ "チョウ","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "広", "answers": [ "コウ","ひろい","ひろがる","ひろげる","ひろまる","ひろめる" ]},
		{ "question": "床", "answers": [ "ショウ","とこ","ゆか" ]},
		{ "question": "序", "answers": [ "ジョ","ついで","はしがき","まなびや" ]},
		{ "question": "底", "answers": [ "テイ","そこ" ]},
		{ "question": "店", "answers": [ "テン","みせ","たな" ]},
		{ "question": "府", "answers": [ "フ","くら","みやこ" ]},
		{ "question": "度", "answers": [ "ド","タク","たび","ト","のり","はかる","めもり","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "座", "answers": [ "ザ","すわる","います" ]},
		{ "question": "庫", "answers": [ "コ","ク","くら" ]},
		{ "question": "庭", "answers": [ "テイ","にわ" ]},
		{ "question": "庶", "answers": [ "ショ","おおい","こいねがう","もろもろ" ]},
		{ "question": "康", "answers": [ "コウ","やすい" ]},
		{ "question": "庸", "answers": [ "ヨウ","おろか","つね","なんぞ","もちいる" ]},
		{ "question": "廃", "answers": [ "ハイ","すたる","すたれる","やめる" ]},
		{ "question": "廉", "answers": [ "レン","いさぎよい","かど","やすい" ]},
		{ "question": "廊", "answers": [ "ロウ","わたどの" ]},
		{ "question": "延", "answers": [ "エン","のばす","のびる","のべる","はえ","ひく" ]},
		{ "question": "廷", "answers": [ "テイ","にわ" ]},
		{ "question": "建", "answers": [ "ケン","たつ","たてる","コン","くつがえす" ]},
		{ "question": "弁", "answers": [ "ベン","かたる","かんむり","とく","はなびら","わきまえる","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "弄", "answers": [ "ロウ","もてあそぶ","あなどる","いじくる","いじる","いらう","たわむれる","まさぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "弊", "answers": [ "ヘイ","ついえる","つかれる","やぶれる" ]},
		{ "question": "式", "answers": [ "シキ","ショク","のっとる","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "弐", "answers": [ "ニ","ジ","ふた","ふたつ" ]},
		{ "question": "弓", "answers": [ "ゆみ","キュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "弔", "answers": [ "チョウ","とむらう" ]},
		{ "question": "引", "answers": [ "イン","ひく","ひける" ]},
		{ "question": "弟", "answers": [ "ダイ","おとうと","デ","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "弥", "answers": [ "や","ビ","ミ","あまねし","いや","いよいよ","つくろう","ひさしい","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "弦", "answers": [ "ゲン","つる" ]},
		{ "question": "弧", "answers": [ "コ","きゆみ" ]},
		{ "question": "弱", "answers": [ "ジャク","よわい","よわまる","よわめる","よわる","ニャク" ]},
		{ "question": "張", "answers": [ "チョウ","はる" ]},
		{ "question": "強", "answers": [ "キョウ","つよい","つよまる","つよめる","ゴウ","しいる","あながち","こわい","したたか","つとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "弾", "answers": [ "ダン","たま","はずむ","ひく","ただす","はじく","はじける","はずみ" ]},
		{ "question": "当", "answers": [ "トウ","あたる","あてる","まさに" ]},
		{ "question": "彙", "answers": [ "イ","あつめる","たぐい","はりねずみ" ]},
		{ "question": "形", "answers": [ "ギョウ","ケイ","かた","かたち","なり" ]},
		{ "question": "彩", "answers": [ "サイ","いろどる","あや" ]},
		{ "question": "彫", "answers": [ "チョウ","ほる" ]},
		{ "question": "彰", "answers": [ "ショウ","あきらか","あらわす","あらわれる" ]},
		{ "question": "影", "answers": [ "エイ","かげ","ヨウ" ]},
		{ "question": "役", "answers": [ "ヤク","エキ","いくさ","つとめ" ]},
		{ "question": "彼", "answers": [ "ヒ","かの","かれ" ]},
		{ "question": "往", "answers": [ "オウ","いにしえ","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "征", "answers": [ "セイ","うつ","とる","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "径", "answers": [ "ケイ","こみち","さしわたし","ただちに","みち" ]},
		{ "question": "待", "answers": [ "タイ","まつ" ]},
		{ "question": "律", "answers": [ "リツ","リチ","のっとる","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "後", "answers": [ "ゴ","コウ","あと","うしろ","のち","おくれる","しり" ]},
		{ "question": "徐", "answers": [ "ジョ","おもむろ" ]},
		{ "question": "徒", "answers": [ "ト","ズ","あだ","いたずらに","かち","ただ","ともがら","むだ" ]},
		{ "question": "従", "answers": [ "ジュウ","したがう","したがえる","ジュ","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "得", "answers": [ "トク","える","うる" ]},
		{ "question": "御", "answers": [ "ギョ","ゴ","おん","お","おさめる","み" ]},
		{ "question": "復", "answers": [ "フク","かえす","かえる","ふたたび","また" ]},
		{ "question": "循", "answers": [ "ジュン","したがう","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "微", "answers": [ "ビ","ミ","かすか" ]},
		{ "question": "徳", "answers": [ "トク" ]},
		{ "question": "徴", "answers": [ "チョウ","チ","しるし","めす" ]},
		{ "question": "徹", "answers": [ "テツ","とおる" ]},
		{ "question": "心", "answers": [ "シン","こころ","うら" ]},
		{ "question": "必", "answers": [ "ヒツ","かならず" ]},
		{ "question": "忌", "answers": [ "キ","いまわしい","いむ" ]},
		{ "question": "忍", "answers": [ "ニン","しのばせる","しのぶ","ジン","むごい" ]},
		{ "question": "志", "answers": [ "シ","こころざし","こころざす","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "忘", "answers": [ "わすれる","ボウ","モウ" ]},
		{ "question": "忙", "answers": [ "ボウ","いそがしい","モウ","せわしい" ]},
		{ "question": "応", "answers": [ "オウ","こたえる","まさに" ]},
		{ "question": "忠", "answers": [ "チュウ","まごころ" ]},
		{ "question": "快", "answers": [ "カイ","こころよい","ケ" ]},
		{ "question": "念", "answers": [ "ネン","おもう" ]},
		{ "question": "怒", "answers": [ "ド","いかる","おこる","ヌ" ]},
		{ "question": "怖", "answers": [ "フ","こわい","おじける","おそれる" ]},
		{ "question": "思", "answers": [ "シ","おもう","おぼしい" ]},
		{ "question": "怠", "answers": [ "タイ","おこたる","なまける","だるい" ]},
		{ "question": "急", "answers": [ "キュウ","いそぐ","せく" ]},
		{ "question": "性", "answers": [ "セイ","ショウ","さが","たち" ]},
		{ "question": "怨", "answers": [ "オン","エン","うらみ","うらむ" ]},
		{ "question": "怪", "answers": [ "カイ","あやしい","あやしむ","ケ" ]},
		{ "question": "恋", "answers": [ "レン","こい","こいしい","こう" ]},
		{ "question": "恐", "answers": [ "キョウ","おそれる","おそろしい","こわい" ]},
		{ "question": "恒", "answers": [ "コウ","つね","つねに" ]},
		{ "question": "恣", "answers": [ "シ","ほしいまま" ]},
		{ "question": "恥", "answers": [ "チ","はじ","はじらう","はじる","はずかしい" ]},
		{ "question": "恨", "answers": [ "コン","うらむ","うらめしい" ]},
		{ "question": "恩", "answers": [ "オン","めぐみ" ]},
		{ "question": "恭", "answers": [ "キョウ","うやうやしい","つつしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "息", "answers": [ "ソク","いき","いこう","やすむ","やむ" ]},
		{ "question": "恵", "answers": [ "エ","ケイ","めぐむ" ]},
		{ "question": "悔", "answers": [ "カイ","くいる","くやしい","くやむ","ケ" ]},
		{ "question": "悟", "answers": [ "ゴ","さとる" ]},
		{ "question": "悠", "answers": [ "ユウ","とおい","はるか" ]},
		{ "question": "患", "answers": [ "カン","わずらう","ゲン","うれい","うれえる","わずらい" ]},
		{ "question": "悦", "answers": [ "エツ","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "悩", "answers": [ "ノウ","なやます","なやむ","ドウ" ]},
		{ "question": "悪", "answers": [ "アク","わるい","オ","あし","いずくんぞ","にくむ" ]},
		{ "question": "悲", "answers": [ "ヒ","かなしい","かなしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "悼", "answers": [ "トウ","いたむ" ]},
		{ "question": "情", "answers": [ "ジョウ","なさけ","セイ","おもむき","こころ" ]},
		{ "question": "惑", "answers": [ "ワク","まどう" ]},
		{ "question": "惜", "answers": [ "セキ","おしい","おしむ","シャク" ]},
		{ "question": "惧", "answers": [ "グ","ク","おそれる" ]},
		{ "question": "惨", "answers": [ "サン","ザン","みじめ","いたましい","いたむ","むごい" ]},
		{ "question": "惰", "answers": [ "ダ","タ","おこたる" ]},
		{ "question": "想", "answers": [ "ソウ","ソ","おもう" ]},
		{ "question": "愁", "answers": [ "シュウ","うれい","うれえる" ]},
		{ "question": "愉", "answers": [ "ユ","たのしい","たのしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "意", "answers": [ "イ","おもう","こころ" ]},
		{ "question": "愚", "answers": [ "グ","おろか" ]},
		{ "question": "愛", "answers": [ "アイ","いとしい","うい","おしむ","かなしい","まな","めでる" ]},
		{ "question": "感", "answers": [ "カン" ]},
		{ "question": "慄", "answers": [ "リツ","おそれる","おののく" ]},
		{ "question": "慈", "answers": [ "ジ","いつくしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "態", "answers": [ "タイ","テイ","さま","わざと" ]},
		{ "question": "慌", "answers": [ "あわただしい","あわてる","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "慎", "answers": [ "シン","つつしむ","つつましい","つつましやか" ]},
		{ "question": "慕", "answers": [ "ボ","したう","しのぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "慢", "answers": [ "マン","バン","あなどる","おこたる","おごる" ]},
		{ "question": "慣", "answers": [ "カン","ならす","なれる","ならわし" ]},
		{ "question": "慨", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","いきどおる","なげく" ]},
		{ "question": "慮", "answers": [ "リョ","おもんぱかる" ]},
		{ "question": "慰", "answers": [ "イ","なぐさむ","なぐさめる" ]},
		{ "question": "慶", "answers": [ "ケイ","キョウ","よい","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "憂", "answers": [ "ユウ","うれい","うれえる","うい" ]},
		{ "question": "憎", "answers": [ "ゾウ","にくい","にくしみ","にくむ","にくらしい","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "憤", "answers": [ "フン","いきどおる","むずかる" ]},
		{ "question": "憧", "answers": [ "ショウ","あこがれる","トウ","ドウ" ]},
		{ "question": "憩", "answers": [ "ケイ","いこい","いこう" ]},
		{ "question": "憬", "answers": [ "ケイ","あこがれる" ]},
		{ "question": "憲", "answers": [ "ケン","のっとる","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "憶", "answers": [ "オク","おぼえる","おもう" ]},
		{ "question": "憾", "answers": [ "カン","うらむ" ]},
		{ "question": "懇", "answers": [ "コン","ねんごろ" ]},
		{ "question": "懐", "answers": [ "カイ","なつかしい","なつかしむ","なつく","なつける","ふところ","いだく","おもう" ]},
		{ "question": "懲", "answers": [ "チョウ","こらしめる","こらす","こりる" ]},
		{ "question": "懸", "answers": [ "ケン","かかる","かける","ケ","へだたる" ]},
		{ "question": "成", "answers": [ "セイ","なす","なる","ジョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "我", "answers": [ "われ","ガ","わ" ]},
		{ "question": "戒", "answers": [ "カイ","いましめる" ]},
		{ "question": "戚", "answers": [ "セキ","いたむ","うれえる","みうち" ]},
		{ "question": "戦", "answers": [ "セン","たたかう","いくさ","おののく","そよぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "戯", "answers": [ "ギ","たわむれる","ゲ","ざれる","たわける" ]},
		{ "question": "戴", "answers": [ "タイ","いただく" ]},
		{ "question": "戸", "answers": [ "コ","と","へ" ]},
		{ "question": "戻", "answers": [ "もどす","もどる","レイ","いたる","もとる" ]},
		{ "question": "房", "answers": [ "ボウ","ふさ","ホウ","いえ","へや" ]},
		{ "question": "所", "answers": [ "ショ","ところ","ソ" ]},
		{ "question": "扇", "answers": [ "セン","おうぎ","あおぐ","おだてる" ]},
		{ "question": "扉", "answers": [ "とびら","ヒ" ]},
		{ "question": "手", "answers": [ "シュ","て","た","ズ" ]},
		{ "question": "才", "answers": [ "サイ","かど","ざえ" ]},
		{ "question": "打", "answers": [ "ダ","うつ","チョウ","テイ","ダス","ぶつ" ]},
		{ "question": "払", "answers": [ "はらう","フツ","ヒツ" ]},
		{ "question": "扱", "answers": [ "あつかう","キュウ","ソウ","こく","しごく" ]},
		{ "question": "扶", "answers": [ "フ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "批", "answers": [ "ヒ","うつ","ただす" ]},
		{ "question": "承", "answers": [ "ショウ","うけたまわる","うける" ]},
		{ "question": "技", "answers": [ "ギ","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "抄", "answers": [ "ショウ","ソウ","うつす","かすめる","すく","すくう" ]},
		{ "question": "把", "answers": [ "ハ","とる","にぎる" ]},
		{ "question": "抑", "answers": [ "ヨク","おさえる","そもそも","ふさぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "投", "answers": [ "トウ","なげる" ]},
		{ "question": "抗", "answers": [ "コウ","あらがう","こばむ","はりあう","ふせぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "折", "answers": [ "セツ","おり","おる","おれる","シャク","くじける","さだめる" ]},
		{ "question": "抜", "answers": [ "バツ","ぬかす","ぬかる","ぬく","ぬける" ]},
		{ "question": "択", "answers": [ "タク","えらぶ","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "披", "answers": [ "ヒ","ひらく" ]},
		{ "question": "抱", "answers": [ "ホウ","いだく","かかえる","だく" ]},
		{ "question": "抵", "answers": [ "テイ","シ","あたる","うつ","ふれる" ]},
		{ "question": "抹", "answers": [ "マツ","バツ","けす","こな","する" ]},
		{ "question": "押", "answers": [ "おさえる","おす","オウ" ]},
		{ "question": "抽", "answers": [ "チュウ","ぬく","ひく" ]},
		{ "question": "担", "answers": [ "タン","かつぐ","になう","ケツ" ]},
		{ "question": "拉", "answers": [ "ラ","ラツ","ロウ","くじく","ひく","ひしぐ","ひしゃげる" ]},
		{ "question": "拍", "answers": [ "ハク","ヒョウ","うつ" ]},
		{ "question": "拐", "answers": [ "カイ","かたる","かどわかす" ]},
		{ "question": "拒", "answers": [ "キョ","こばむ","ふせぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "拓", "answers": [ "タク","セキ","ひらく" ]},
		{ "question": "拘", "answers": [ "コウ","かかわる","こだわる","とどめる","とらえる" ]},
		{ "question": "拙", "answers": [ "セツ","つたない","まずい" ]},
		{ "question": "招", "answers": [ "ショウ","まねく" ]},
		{ "question": "拝", "answers": [ "ハイ","おがむ" ]},
		{ "question": "拠", "answers": [ "キョ","コ","よりどころ","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "拡", "answers": [ "カク","ひろがる","ひろげる" ]},
		{ "question": "括", "answers": [ "カツ","くくる","くびる","くびれる" ]},
		{ "question": "拭", "answers": [ "ぬぐう","ふく","ショク","シキ" ]},
		{ "question": "拳", "answers": [ "ケン","こぶし","ゲン" ]},
		{ "question": "拶", "answers": [ "サツ","せまる" ]},
		{ "question": "拷", "answers": [ "ゴウ","コウ","うつ" ]},
		{ "question": "拾", "answers": [ "ひろう","シュウ","ジュウ","とお" ]},
		{ "question": "持", "answers": [ "ジ","もつ","チ" ]},
		{ "question": "指", "answers": [ "シ","さす","ゆび" ]},
		{ "question": "挑", "answers": [ "チョウ","いどむ","トウ" ]},
		{ "question": "挙", "answers": [ "キョ","あがる","あげる","こぞって","こぞる" ]},
		{ "question": "挟", "answers": [ "はさまる","はさむ","キョウ","さしはさむ" ]},
		{ "question": "挨", "answers": [ "アイ","おす","ひらく" ]},
		{ "question": "挫", "answers": [ "ザ","くじく","くじける" ]},
		{ "question": "振", "answers": [ "シン","ふる","ふるう","ふれる","すくう" ]},
		{ "question": "挿", "answers": [ "ソウ","さす","さしはさむ","すげる","はさむ" ]},
		{ "question": "捉", "answers": [ "ソク","とらえる","つかまえる","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "捕", "answers": [ "ホ","つかまえる","つかまる","とらえる","とらわれる","とる","ブ" ]},
		{ "question": "捗", "answers": [ "チョク","はかどる" ]},
		{ "question": "捜", "answers": [ "ソウ","さがす" ]},
		{ "question": "捨", "answers": [ "シャ","すてる","ほどこす" ]},
		{ "question": "据", "answers": [ "すえる","すわる","キョ" ]},
		{ "question": "捻", "answers": [ "ネン","デン","ねじる","ひねる" ]},
		{ "question": "掃", "answers": [ "ソウ","はく","はらう" ]},
		{ "question": "授", "answers": [ "ジュ","さずかる","さずける" ]},
		{ "question": "掌", "answers": [ "ショウ","たなごころ","つかさどる","てのひら" ]},
		{ "question": "排", "answers": [ "ハイ","おしのける","つらねる" ]},
		{ "question": "掘", "answers": [ "クツ","ほる" ]},
		{ "question": "掛", "answers": [ "かかり","かかる","かける" ]},
		{ "question": "採", "answers": [ "サイ","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "探", "answers": [ "タン","さがす","さぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "接", "answers": [ "セツ","つぐ","ショウ","はぐ","まじわる","もてなす" ]},
		{ "question": "控", "answers": [ "ひかえる","コウ","つげる","のぞく" ]},
		{ "question": "推", "answers": [ "スイ","おす" ]},
		{ "question": "措", "answers": [ "ソ","サク","おく","はからう" ]},
		{ "question": "掲", "answers": [ "ケイ","かかげる" ]},
		{ "question": "描", "answers": [ "ビョウ","えがく","かく" ]},
		{ "question": "提", "answers": [ "テイ","さげる","ダイ","チョウ","ひさげ","ひっさげる" ]},
		{ "question": "揚", "answers": [ "ヨウ","あがる","あげる" ]},
		{ "question": "換", "answers": [ "カン","かえる","かわる" ]},
		{ "question": "握", "answers": [ "アク","にぎる" ]},
		{ "question": "揮", "answers": [ "キ","ふるう" ]},
		{ "question": "援", "answers": [ "エン","たすける","ひく" ]},
		{ "question": "揺", "answers": [ "ヨウ","ゆさぶる","ゆすぶる","ゆする","ゆらぐ","ゆる","ゆるぐ","ゆれる" ]},
		{ "question": "損", "answers": [ "ソン","そこなう","そこねる","へる" ]},
		{ "question": "搬", "answers": [ "ハン","はこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "搭", "answers": [ "トウ","のせる","のる" ]},
		{ "question": "携", "answers": [ "ケイ","たずさえる","たずさわる","はなれる" ]},
		{ "question": "搾", "answers": [ "しぼる","サク" ]},
		{ "question": "摂", "answers": [ "セツ","ショウ","かねる","かわる","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "摘", "answers": [ "テキ","つむ","つまむ" ]},
		{ "question": "摩", "answers": [ "マ","こする","さする","する" ]},
		{ "question": "摯", "answers": [ "シ","あらい","とる","にえ","まこと" ]},
		{ "question": "撃", "answers": [ "ゲキ","うつ","ケキ" ]},
		{ "question": "撤", "answers": [ "テツ","すてる" ]},
		{ "question": "撮", "answers": [ "サツ","とる","つまむ" ]},
		{ "question": "撲", "answers": [ "ボク","ホク","うつ","なぐる","はる" ]},
		{ "question": "擁", "answers": [ "ヨウ","いだく","だく","まもる" ]},
		{ "question": "操", "answers": [ "ソウ","あやつる","みさお","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "擦", "answers": [ "サツ","する","すれる","かすれる","こする","さする","なする" ]},
		{ "question": "擬", "answers": [ "ギ","なぞらえる","はかる","まがい","もどき" ]},
		{ "question": "支", "answers": [ "シ","ささえる","かう","つかえる" ]},
		{ "question": "改", "answers": [ "カイ","あらたまる","あらためる" ]},
		{ "question": "攻", "answers": [ "コウ","せめる","おさめる","みがく" ]},
		{ "question": "放", "answers": [ "ホウ","はなす","はなつ","はなれる","ほうる","こく","さく","ひる","ほしいまま","まかす","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "政", "answers": [ "セイ","ショウ","まつりごと" ]},
		{ "question": "故", "answers": [ "コ","ゆえ","ことさらに","ふるい","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "敏", "answers": [ "ビン","さとい","とし" ]},
		{ "question": "救", "answers": [ "キュウ","すくう","ク","グ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "敗", "answers": [ "ハイ","やぶれる","まける","やぶる" ]},
		{ "question": "教", "answers": [ "キョウ","おしえる","おそわる" ]},
		{ "question": "敢", "answers": [ "カン","あえて" ]},
		{ "question": "散", "answers": [ "サン","ちらかす","ちらかる","ちらす","ちる","ばら" ]},
		{ "question": "敬", "answers": [ "ケイ","うやまう","キョウ","つつしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "数", "answers": [ "スウ","かず","かぞえる","ス","サク","シュ","ソク","しばしば" ]},
		{ "question": "整", "answers": [ "セイ","ととのう","ととのえる" ]},
		{ "question": "敵", "answers": [ "テキ","かたき","あだ","かなう" ]},
		{ "question": "敷", "answers": [ "しく","フ" ]},
		{ "question": "文", "answers": [ "ブン","モン","ふみ","あや","かざる" ]},
		{ "question": "斉", "answers": [ "セイ","サイ","シ","ととのえる","ひとしい","ものいみ" ]},
		{ "question": "斎", "answers": [ "サイ","いつく","つつしむ","とき","ものいみ" ]},
		{ "question": "斑", "answers": [ "ハン","ふ","ぶち","まだら" ]},
		{ "question": "斗", "answers": [ "ト","トウ","ひしゃく","ます" ]},
		{ "question": "料", "answers": [ "リョウ","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "斜", "answers": [ "シャ","ななめ","はす" ]},
		{ "question": "斤", "answers": [ "キン","おの" ]},
		{ "question": "斥", "answers": [ "セキ","うかがう","しりぞける" ]},
		{ "question": "斬", "answers": [ "ザン","きる","サン" ]},
		{ "question": "断", "answers": [ "ダン","ことわる","たつ","さだめる" ]},
		{ "question": "新", "answers": [ "シン","あたらしい","あらた","にい","さら" ]},
		{ "question": "方", "answers": [ "ホウ","かた","かく","ただしい","まさに" ]},
		{ "question": "施", "answers": [ "シ","ほどこす","セ","しく" ]},
		{ "question": "旅", "answers": [ "リョ","たび","ロ","いくさ" ]},
		{ "question": "旋", "answers": [ "セン","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "族", "answers": [ "ゾク","やから" ]},
		{ "question": "旗", "answers": [ "キ","はた" ]},
		{ "question": "既", "answers": [ "キ","すでに" ]},
		{ "question": "日", "answers": [ "ジツ","ニチ","か","ひ" ]},
		{ "question": "旦", "answers": [ "タン","ダン","あした" ]},
		{ "question": "旧", "answers": [ "キュウ","ふる","ふるい","ふるびる","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "旨", "answers": [ "シ","むね","うまい" ]},
		{ "question": "早", "answers": [ "ソウ","はやい","はやまる","はやめる","サッ","さ" ]},
		{ "question": "旬", "answers": [ "シュン","ジュン" ]},
		{ "question": "旺", "answers": [ "オウ","さかん" ]},
		{ "question": "昆", "answers": [ "コン","あに" ]},
		{ "question": "昇", "answers": [ "ショウ","のぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "明", "answers": [ "ミョウ","メイ","あかす","あからむ","あかり","あかるい","あかるむ","あきらか","あく","あくる","あける","ミン" ]},
		{ "question": "易", "answers": [ "イ","エキ","やさしい","あなどる","かえる","かわる","やすい" ]},
		{ "question": "昔", "answers": [ "むかし","シャク","セキ" ]},
		{ "question": "星", "answers": [ "セイ","ほし","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "映", "answers": [ "エイ","うつす","うつる","はえる","はやす" ]},
		{ "question": "春", "answers": [ "シュン","はる" ]},
		{ "question": "昧", "answers": [ "マイ","バイ","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "昨", "answers": [ "サク","きのう" ]},
		{ "question": "昭", "answers": [ "ショウ","あきらか" ]},
		{ "question": "是", "answers": [ "ゼ","シ","この","これ","ただしい" ]},
		{ "question": "昼", "answers": [ "チュウ","ひる" ]},
		{ "question": "時", "answers": [ "ジ","とき" ]},
		{ "question": "晩", "answers": [ "バン","おそい","くれ" ]},
		{ "question": "普", "answers": [ "フ","あまねく" ]},
		{ "question": "景", "answers": [ "ケイ","エイ" ]},
		{ "question": "晴", "answers": [ "セイ","はらす","はれる" ]},
		{ "question": "晶", "answers": [ "ショウ","あきらか" ]},
		{ "question": "暁", "answers": [ "あかつき","ギョウ","さとる" ]},
		{ "question": "暇", "answers": [ "カ","ひま","いとま" ]},
		{ "question": "暑", "answers": [ "ショ","あつい" ]},
		{ "question": "暖", "answers": [ "ダン","あたたか","あたたかい","あたたまる","あたためる","ノン" ]},
		{ "question": "暗", "answers": [ "アン","くらい","そらんじる","やみ" ]},
		{ "question": "暦", "answers": [ "レキ","こよみ","リャク" ]},
		{ "question": "暫", "answers": [ "ザン","しばし","しばらく" ]},
		{ "question": "暮", "answers": [ "くらす","くれる","ボ" ]},
		{ "question": "暴", "answers": [ "ボウ","あばれる","バク","あばく","あらい","あらわす","さらす","にわか" ]},
		{ "question": "曇", "answers": [ "ドン","くもる","タン" ]},
		{ "question": "曖", "answers": [ "アイ","おおう","かげる","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "曜", "answers": [ "ヨウ","かがやく" ]},
		{ "question": "曲", "answers": [ "キョク","まがる","まげる","かね","くせ","くま","まが" ]},
		{ "question": "更", "answers": [ "コウ","さら","ふかす","ふける","あらためる","かえる" ]},
		{ "question": "書", "answers": [ "ショ","かく","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "曹", "answers": [ "ソウ","ゾウ","つかさ","ともがら" ]},
		{ "question": "曽", "answers": [ "ゾ","ソウ","ソ","ゾウ","かさなる","かつて","すなわち","ます" ]},
		{ "question": "替", "answers": [ "タイ","かえる","かわる","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "最", "answers": [ "サイ","もっとも","も" ]},
		{ "question": "月", "answers": [ "ガツ","ゲツ","つき" ]},
		{ "question": "有", "answers": [ "ユウ","ある","ウ","もつ" ]},
		{ "question": "服", "answers": [ "フク","きもの","きる","したがう","のむ" ]},
		{ "question": "朕", "answers": [ "チン","きざし","われ" ]},
		{ "question": "朗", "answers": [ "ロウ","ほがらか","あきらか","たからか" ]},
		{ "question": "望", "answers": [ "ボウ","のぞむ","モウ","うらむ","もち" ]},
		{ "question": "朝", "answers": [ "チョウ","あさ","あした" ]},
		{ "question": "期", "answers": [ "キ","ゴ","きめる","ちぎる","とき" ]},
		{ "question": "木", "answers": [ "ボク","モク","き","こ" ]},
		{ "question": "未", "answers": [ "ミ","ビ","いまだ","ひつじ","まだ" ]},
		{ "question": "末", "answers": [ "マツ","すえ","バツ","うら" ]},
		{ "question": "本", "answers": [ "ホン","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "札", "answers": [ "サツ","ふだ","さね","わかじに" ]},
		{ "question": "朱", "answers": [ "シュ","ス","あか","あかい","あけ" ]},
		{ "question": "朴", "answers": [ "ボク","ハク","えのき","すなお","ほお" ]},
		{ "question": "机", "answers": [ "つくえ","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "朽", "answers": [ "キュウ","くちる","すたれる" ]},
		{ "question": "杉", "answers": [ "すぎ","サン" ]},
		{ "question": "材", "answers": [ "ザイ","サイ","まるた" ]},
		{ "question": "村", "answers": [ "ソン","むら" ]},
		{ "question": "束", "answers": [ "ソク","たば","つか","つかねる" ]},
		{ "question": "条", "answers": [ "ジョウ","えだ","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "来", "answers": [ "ライ","くる","きたす","きたる","きし","こし" ]},
		{ "question": "杯", "answers": [ "ハイ","さかずき" ]},
		{ "question": "東", "answers": [ "トウ","ひがし","あずま" ]},
		{ "question": "松", "answers": [ "ショウ","まつ" ]},
		{ "question": "板", "answers": [ "ハン","バン","いた" ]},
		{ "question": "析", "answers": [ "セキ","さく","わかれる","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "枕", "answers": [ "まくら","シン","チン" ]},
		{ "question": "林", "answers": [ "リン","はやし","おおい" ]},
		{ "question": "枚", "answers": [ "マイ","バイ","ひら" ]},
		{ "question": "果", "answers": [ "カ","はたす","はて","はてる","おおせる","くだもの","はか" ]},
		{ "question": "枝", "answers": [ "えだ","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "枠", "answers": [ "わく" ]},
		{ "question": "枢", "answers": [ "スウ","かなめ","とぼそ" ]},
		{ "question": "枯", "answers": [ "コ","からす","かれる","からびる" ]},
		{ "question": "架", "answers": [ "カ","かかる","かける","たな" ]},
		{ "question": "柄", "answers": [ "え","がら","ヘイ","いきおい","つか" ]},
		{ "question": "某", "answers": [ "ボウ","バイ","それがし","なにがし" ]},
		{ "question": "染", "answers": [ "そまる","そめる","セン","しみ","しみる","ゼン" ]},
		{ "question": "柔", "answers": [ "ジュウ","ニュウ","やわらか","やわらかい","やさしい","やわらげる" ]},
		{ "question": "柱", "answers": [ "チュウ","はしら" ]},
		{ "question": "柳", "answers": [ "リュウ","やなぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "柵", "answers": [ "サク","しがらみ","とりで","やらい" ]},
		{ "question": "査", "answers": [ "サ","しらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "柿", "answers": [ "かき","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "栃", "answers": [ "とち" ]},
		{ "question": "栄", "answers": [ "エイ","さかえる","はえ","はえる","はやす" ]},
		{ "question": "栓", "answers": [ "セン" ]},
		{ "question": "校", "answers": [ "コウ","キョウ","あぜ","かせ","かんがえる","くらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "株", "answers": [ "かぶ","シュ" ]},
		{ "question": "核", "answers": [ "カク","さね" ]},
		{ "question": "根", "answers": [ "コン","ね" ]},
		{ "question": "格", "answers": [ "カク","コウ","キャク","ゴウ","いたる","うつ","ただす" ]},
		{ "question": "栽", "answers": [ "サイ","うえる" ]},
		{ "question": "桁", "answers": [ "けた","コウ","かせ" ]},
		{ "question": "桃", "answers": [ "トウ","もも" ]},
		{ "question": "案", "answers": [ "アン","かんがえる","つくえ" ]},
		{ "question": "桑", "answers": [ "くわ","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "桜", "answers": [ "さくら","オウ" ]},
		{ "question": "桟", "answers": [ "サン","かけはし","たな" ]},
		{ "question": "梅", "answers": [ "バイ","うめ" ]},
		{ "question": "梗", "answers": [ "コウ","キョウ","おおむね","かたい","つよい","でく","ふさがる" ]},
		{ "question": "梨", "answers": [ "なし","リ" ]},
		{ "question": "械", "answers": [ "カイ","かせ","からくり" ]},
		{ "question": "棄", "answers": [ "キ","すてる" ]},
		{ "question": "棋", "answers": [ "キ","ゴ" ]},
		{ "question": "棒", "answers": [ "ボウ","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "棚", "answers": [ "たな","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "棟", "answers": [ "トウ","むね","むな","かしら" ]},
		{ "question": "森", "answers": [ "シン","もり" ]},
		{ "question": "棺", "answers": [ "カン","ひつぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "椅", "answers": [ "イ" ]},
		{ "question": "植", "answers": [ "ショク","うえる","うわる","チ","たてる" ]},
		{ "question": "椎", "answers": [ "ツイ","スイ","うつ","しい","せぼね","つち" ]},
		{ "question": "検", "answers": [ "ケン","あらためる","しらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "業", "answers": [ "ギョウ","わざ","ゴウ" ]},
		{ "question": "極", "answers": [ "キョク","ゴク","きわまる","きわみ","きわめる","きまる","きめる" ]},
		{ "question": "楷", "answers": [ "カイ","のっとる","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "楼", "answers": [ "ロウ","たかどの","やぐら" ]},
		{ "question": "楽", "answers": [ "ガク","ラク","たのしい","たのしむ","ギョウ","ゴウ","かなでる","このむ" ]},
		{ "question": "概", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","おおむね" ]},
		{ "question": "構", "answers": [ "コウ","かまう","かまえる" ]},
		{ "question": "様", "answers": [ "ヨウ","さま" ]},
		{ "question": "槽", "answers": [ "ソウ","おけ","かいばおけ","ふね" ]},
		{ "question": "標", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","こずえ","しめ","しるし","しるす","しるべ" ]},
		{ "question": "模", "answers": [ "ボ","モ","かた","のっとる" ]},
		{ "question": "権", "answers": [ "ケン","ゴン","いきおい","おもり","かり","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "横", "answers": [ "オウ","よこ","コウ","よこたわる" ]},
		{ "question": "樹", "answers": [ "ジュ","うえる","き","たてる" ]},
		{ "question": "橋", "answers": [ "キョウ","はし" ]},
		{ "question": "機", "answers": [ "キ","はた","おり","からくり","きざし","はずみ" ]},
		{ "question": "欄", "answers": [ "ラン","おばしま","おり","てすり","わく" ]},
		{ "question": "欠", "answers": [ "ケツ","かく","かける","ケン","あくび" ]},
		{ "question": "次", "answers": [ "ジ","つぎ","つぐ","シ","ついず","やどる" ]},
		{ "question": "欧", "answers": [ "オウ","はく" ]},
		{ "question": "欲", "answers": [ "ヨク","ほしい","ほっする" ]},
		{ "question": "欺", "answers": [ "ギ","あざむく","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "款", "answers": [ "カン","しるす","たたく","まこと","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "歌", "answers": [ "カ","うた","うたう" ]},
		{ "question": "歓", "answers": [ "カン","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "止", "answers": [ "シ","とまる","とめる","さす","とどまる","とどめる","やむ","やめる","よす" ]},
		{ "question": "正", "answers": [ "ショウ","セイ","ただしい","ただす","まさ" ]},
		{ "question": "武", "answers": [ "ブ","ム","たけし","もののふ" ]},
		{ "question": "歩", "answers": [ "ホ","あゆむ","あるく","ブ","フ" ]},
		{ "question": "歯", "answers": [ "シ","は","よわい" ]},
		{ "question": "歳", "answers": [ "サイ","セイ","とし","とせ","よわい" ]},
		{ "question": "歴", "answers": [ "レキ","リャク","へる" ]},
		{ "question": "死", "answers": [ "シ","しぬ" ]},
		{ "question": "殉", "answers": [ "ジュン","したがう" ]},
		{ "question": "殊", "answers": [ "シュ","こと" ]},
		{ "question": "残", "answers": [ "ザン","のこす","のこる","そこなう" ]},
		{ "question": "殖", "answers": [ "ショク","ふえる","ふやす" ]},
		{ "question": "殴", "answers": [ "なぐる","オウ","うつ","たたく" ]},
		{ "question": "段", "answers": [ "ダン","タン","きざはし" ]},
		{ "question": "殺", "answers": [ "サツ","ころす","サイ","セツ","あやめる","けずる","そぐ","そげる" ]},
		{ "question": "殻", "answers": [ "カク","から" ]},
		{ "question": "殿", "answers": [ "テン","デン","との","どの","しんがり" ]},
		{ "question": "毀", "answers": [ "キ","こぼつ","こわす","そしる","やせる","やぶる","やぶれる" ]},
		{ "question": "母", "answers": [ "ボ","はは","ボウ","モ" ]},
		{ "question": "毎", "answers": [ "マイ","バイ","ごと","つね","むさぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "毒", "answers": [ "ドク","そこなう","わるい" ]},
		{ "question": "比", "answers": [ "ヒ","くらべる","ビ","ころ","たぐい","ならぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "毛", "answers": [ "モウ","け","ボウ" ]},
		{ "question": "氏", "answers": [ "シ","うじ" ]},
		{ "question": "民", "answers": [ "ミン","たみ" ]},
		{ "question": "気", "answers": [ "キ","ケ","いき" ]},
		{ "question": "水", "answers": [ "スイ","みず" ]},
		{ "question": "氷", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","こおり","ひ","こおる" ]},
		{ "question": "永", "answers": [ "エイ","ながい","ヨウ","とこしえ" ]},
		{ "question": "氾", "answers": [ "ハン","あふれる","ひろがる" ]},
		{ "question": "汁", "answers": [ "ジュウ","しる","シュウ","つゆ" ]},
		{ "question": "求", "answers": [ "キュウ","もとめる","グ" ]},
		{ "question": "汎", "answers": [ "ハン","フウ","ホウ","あふれる","うかぶ","ひろい" ]},
		{ "question": "汗", "answers": [ "カン","あせ" ]},
		{ "question": "汚", "answers": [ "オ","きたない","よごす","よごれる","けがす","けがらわしい","けがれる" ]},
		{ "question": "江", "answers": [ "コウ","え" ]},
		{ "question": "池", "answers": [ "チ","いけ" ]},
		{ "question": "汰", "answers": [ "タ","タイ","おごる","にごる","よなげる" ]},
		{ "question": "決", "answers": [ "ケツ","きまる","きめる" ]},
		{ "question": "汽", "answers": [ "キ","ゆげ" ]},
		{ "question": "沃", "answers": [ "ヨク","オク","こえる","そそぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "沈", "answers": [ "チン","しずむ","しずめる","ジン" ]},
		{ "question": "沖", "answers": [ "おき","チュウ","とぶ","むなしい" ]},
		{ "question": "沙", "answers": [ "サ","シャ","すな","みぎわ","よなげる" ]},
		{ "question": "没", "answers": [ "ボツ","モツ","おぼれる","しずむ","しぬ","ない" ]},
		{ "question": "沢", "answers": [ "タク","さわ","うるおう","つや" ]},
		{ "question": "河", "answers": [ "カ","かわ" ]},
		{ "question": "沸", "answers": [ "フツ","わかす","わく","ヒ","たてる","にえ" ]},
		{ "question": "油", "answers": [ "ユ","あぶら","ユウ" ]},
		{ "question": "治", "answers": [ "ジ","チ","おさまる","おさめる","なおす","なおる" ]},
		{ "question": "沼", "answers": [ "ぬま","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "沿", "answers": [ "エン","そう","ふち" ]},
		{ "question": "況", "answers": [ "キョウ","ありさま","いわんや" ]},
		{ "question": "泉", "answers": [ "セン","いずみ" ]},
		{ "question": "泊", "answers": [ "ハク","とまる","とめる" ]},
		{ "question": "泌", "answers": [ "ヒツ","ヒ","にじむ" ]},
		{ "question": "法", "answers": [ "ホウ","ハッ","ホッ","のっとる","のり","フラン" ]},
		{ "question": "泡", "answers": [ "ホウ","あわ","あぶく" ]},
		{ "question": "波", "answers": [ "ハ","なみ" ]},
		{ "question": "泣", "answers": [ "なく","キュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "泥", "answers": [ "どろ","デイ","なずむ" ]},
		{ "question": "注", "answers": [ "チュウ","そそぐ","さす","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "泰", "answers": [ "タイ","おごる","やすい","やすらか" ]},
		{ "question": "泳", "answers": [ "エイ","およぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "洋", "answers": [ "ヨウ","うみ","なだ","ひろい" ]},
		{ "question": "洗", "answers": [ "セン","あらう","セイ" ]},
		{ "question": "洞", "answers": [ "ドウ","ほら","トウ","うつろ","うろ","つらぬく","ふかい" ]},
		{ "question": "津", "answers": [ "つ","シン","しる" ]},
		{ "question": "洪", "answers": [ "コウ","おおみず" ]},
		{ "question": "活", "answers": [ "カツ","いかす","いきる","いける" ]},
		{ "question": "派", "answers": [ "ハ","ハイ","つかわす","わかれる" ]},
		{ "question": "流", "answers": [ "リュウ","ながす","ながれる","ル" ]},
		{ "question": "浄", "answers": [ "ジョウ","きよい" ]},
		{ "question": "浅", "answers": [ "あさい","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "浜", "answers": [ "ヒン","はま","ヒョウ","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "浦", "answers": [ "うら","ホ" ]},
		{ "question": "浪", "answers": [ "ロウ","ラン","なみ","みだりに" ]},
		{ "question": "浮", "answers": [ "フ","うかぶ","うかべる","うかれる","うく","ブ","フウ" ]},
		{ "question": "浴", "answers": [ "ヨク","あびせる","あびる","ゆあみ" ]},
		{ "question": "海", "answers": [ "カイ","うみ" ]},
		{ "question": "浸", "answers": [ "シン","ひたす","ひたる","しみる","つかる","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "消", "answers": [ "ショウ","きえる","けす" ]},
		{ "question": "涙", "answers": [ "ルイ","なみだ" ]},
		{ "question": "涯", "answers": [ "ガイ","はて","みぎわ" ]},
		{ "question": "液", "answers": [ "エキ","しる","わき" ]},
		{ "question": "涼", "answers": [ "リョウ","すずしい","すずむ","うすい" ]},
		{ "question": "淑", "answers": [ "シュク","しとやか","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "淡", "answers": [ "タン","あわい","うすい" ]},
		{ "question": "淫", "answers": [ "イン","あふれる","おおきい","ながあめ","ふける","ほしいまま","みだす","みだら" ]},
		{ "question": "深", "answers": [ "シン","ふかい","ふかまる","ふかめる","ふける","み" ]},
		{ "question": "混", "answers": [ "コン","こむ","まざる","まじる","まぜる" ]},
		{ "question": "添", "answers": [ "テン","そう","そえる" ]},
		{ "question": "清", "answers": [ "セイ","きよい","きよまる","きよめる","ショウ","シン","さやか","すむ" ]},
		{ "question": "渇", "answers": [ "かわく","カツ","ケツ","むさぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "済", "answers": [ "サイ","すます","すむ","セイ","すくう","なす","わたす","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "渉", "answers": [ "ショウ","かかわる","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "渋", "answers": [ "ジュウ","しぶ","しぶい","しぶる","シュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "渓", "answers": [ "ケイ","たに" ]},
		{ "question": "減", "answers": [ "ゲン","へらす","へる" ]},
		{ "question": "渡", "answers": [ "ト","わたす","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "渦", "answers": [ "うず","カ" ]},
		{ "question": "温", "answers": [ "オン","あたたか","あたたかい","あたたまる","あたためる","ウン","たずねる","つつむ","ぬくい","ぬくまる","ぬくめる","ぬるい" ]},
		{ "question": "測", "answers": [ "ソク","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "港", "answers": [ "コウ","みなと" ]},
		{ "question": "湖", "answers": [ "コ","みずうみ" ]},
		{ "question": "湧", "answers": [ "ユウ","わく","ヨウ" ]},
		{ "question": "湯", "answers": [ "トウ","ゆ","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "湾", "answers": [ "ワン","いりえ" ]},
		{ "question": "湿", "answers": [ "シツ","しめす","しめる","うるおい","うるおす" ]},
		{ "question": "満", "answers": [ "マン","みたす","みちる","バン" ]},
		{ "question": "源", "answers": [ "ゲン","みなもと" ]},
		{ "question": "準", "answers": [ "ジュン","シュン","セツ","なぞらえる","みずもり" ]},
		{ "question": "溝", "answers": [ "コウ","みぞ","どぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "溶", "answers": [ "ヨウ","とかす","とく","とける" ]},
		{ "question": "溺", "answers": [ "デキ","おぼれる","ジョウ","ニョウ","いばり","ゆばり" ]},
		{ "question": "滅", "answers": [ "メツ","ほろびる","ほろぼす","ベツ" ]},
		{ "question": "滋", "answers": [ "ジ","シ","しげる","ます" ]},
		{ "question": "滑", "answers": [ "カツ","コツ","すべる","なめらか","ぬめる" ]},
		{ "question": "滝", "answers": [ "たき","ロウ" ]},
		{ "question": "滞", "answers": [ "タイ","とどこおる" ]},
		{ "question": "滴", "answers": [ "テキ","しずく","したたる","たれる" ]},
		{ "question": "漁", "answers": [ "ギョ","リョウ","あさる","いさり","すなどる" ]},
		{ "question": "漂", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","ただよう","さらす" ]},
		{ "question": "漆", "answers": [ "シツ","うるし","シチ" ]},
		{ "question": "漏", "answers": [ "ロウ","もらす","もる","もれる" ]},
		{ "question": "演", "answers": [ "エン","おこなう","のべる" ]},
		{ "question": "漠", "answers": [ "バク","マク","すなはら","ひろい" ]},
		{ "question": "漢", "answers": [ "カン","おとこ","から" ]},
		{ "question": "漫", "answers": [ "マン","バン","そぞろに","みだりに" ]},
		{ "question": "漬", "answers": [ "つかる","つける","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "漸", "answers": [ "ゼン","ザン","セン","すすむ","やや","ようやく" ]},
		{ "question": "潔", "answers": [ "ケツ","いさぎよい","きよい" ]},
		{ "question": "潜", "answers": [ "セン","ひそむ","もぐる","くぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "潟", "answers": [ "かた","セキ" ]},
		{ "question": "潤", "answers": [ "ジュン","うるおう","うるおす","うるむ","ほとびる" ]},
		{ "question": "潮", "answers": [ "チョウ","しお","うしお" ]},
		{ "question": "潰", "answers": [ "カイ","つぶす","つぶれる","ついえる","みだれる" ]},
		{ "question": "澄", "answers": [ "すます","すむ","チョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "激", "answers": [ "ゲキ","はげしい","はげます" ]},
		{ "question": "濁", "answers": [ "ダク","にごす","にごる","ジョク" ]},
		{ "question": "濃", "answers": [ "ノウ","こい","ジョウ","こまやか" ]},
		{ "question": "濫", "answers": [ "ラン","うかべる","みだりに","みだれる" ]},
		{ "question": "濯", "answers": [ "タク","あらう","すすぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "瀬", "answers": [ "せ","ライ" ]},
		{ "question": "火", "answers": [ "カ","ひ","ほ","コ" ]},
		{ "question": "灯", "answers": [ "トウ","ひ","チョウ","チン","テイ","ドン","あかし","あかり","とぼし","とぼす","ともし","ともしび","ともす","ともる" ]},
		{ "question": "灰", "answers": [ "はい","カイ","ケ" ]},
		{ "question": "災", "answers": [ "サイ","わざわい" ]},
		{ "question": "炉", "answers": [ "ロ","いろり","ひばち" ]},
		{ "question": "炊", "answers": [ "スイ","たく","かしぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "炎", "answers": [ "エン","ほのお","ほむら","もえる" ]},
		{ "question": "炭", "answers": [ "タン","すみ" ]},
		{ "question": "点", "answers": [ "テン","たてる","つける","とぼす","とぼる","ともる" ]},
		{ "question": "為", "answers": [ "イ","する","ため","つくる","なす","なる" ]},
		{ "question": "烈", "answers": [ "レツ","はげしい" ]},
		{ "question": "無", "answers": [ "ブ","ム","ない" ]},
		{ "question": "焦", "answers": [ "ショウ","こがす","こがれる","こげる","あせる","じらす","じれる","やく" ]},
		{ "question": "然", "answers": [ "ゼン","ネン","しかし","しかして","しかも","しからば","しかり","もえる" ]},
		{ "question": "焼", "answers": [ "やく","やける","ショウ","くべる" ]},
		{ "question": "煎", "answers": [ "セン","いる","にる" ]},
		{ "question": "煙", "answers": [ "エン","けむい","けむり","けむる","けぶる","けむ" ]},
		{ "question": "照", "answers": [ "ショウ","てらす","てる","てれる" ]},
		{ "question": "煩", "answers": [ "ハン","わずらう","わずらわす","ボン","うるさい" ]},
		{ "question": "煮", "answers": [ "にえる","にやす","にる","シャ" ]},
		{ "question": "熊", "answers": [ "くま","ユウ" ]},
		{ "question": "熟", "answers": [ "ジュク","うれる","うむ","こなす","こなれる","つくづく","つらつら","なれる","にえる","にる" ]},
		{ "question": "熱", "answers": [ "ネツ","あつい","いきる","ほてる","ほとぼり" ]},
		{ "question": "燃", "answers": [ "ネン","もえる","もす","もやす","ゼン" ]},
		{ "question": "燥", "answers": [ "ソウ","かわく","はしゃぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "爆", "answers": [ "バク","ハク","ホウ","さける","はぜる" ]},
		{ "question": "爪", "answers": [ "つま","つめ","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "爵", "answers": [ "シャク","さかずき" ]},
		{ "question": "父", "answers": [ "フ","ちち","ブ","ホ" ]},
		{ "question": "爽", "answers": [ "ソウ","さわやか","ショウ","あきらか","たがう" ]},
		{ "question": "片", "answers": [ "かた","ヘン","きれ","ひら","ペンス" ]},
		{ "question": "版", "answers": [ "ハン","いた","ふだ" ]},
		{ "question": "牙", "answers": [ "ゲ","きば","ガ","さいとり","は" ]},
		{ "question": "牛", "answers": [ "ギュウ","うし","ゴ" ]},
		{ "question": "牧", "answers": [ "ボク","まき","モク","かう","つかさ","やしなう" ]},
		{ "question": "物", "answers": [ "ブツ","モツ","もの" ]},
		{ "question": "牲", "answers": [ "セイ","いけにえ" ]},
		{ "question": "特", "answers": [ "トク","ドク","おうし","とりわけ","ひとつ","ひとり" ]},
		{ "question": "犠", "answers": [ "ギ","キ","いけにえ" ]},
		{ "question": "犬", "answers": [ "ケン","いぬ" ]},
		{ "question": "犯", "answers": [ "ハン","おかす","ボン" ]},
		{ "question": "状", "answers": [ "ジョウ","かきつけ","かたち" ]},
		{ "question": "狂", "answers": [ "キョウ","くるう","くるおしい","ふれる" ]},
		{ "question": "狙", "answers": [ "ソ","ねらう","さる" ]},
		{ "question": "狩", "answers": [ "シュ","かり","かる" ]},
		{ "question": "独", "answers": [ "ドク","ひとり","トク" ]},
		{ "question": "狭", "answers": [ "せばまる","せばめる","せまい","キョウ","コウ","さ" ]},
		{ "question": "猛", "answers": [ "モウ","たけし" ]},
		{ "question": "猟", "answers": [ "リョウ","かり","かる" ]},
		{ "question": "猫", "answers": [ "ねこ","ビョウ","ミョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "献", "answers": [ "ケン","コン","ささげる","たてまつる","まつる" ]},
		{ "question": "猶", "answers": [ "ユウ","なお" ]},
		{ "question": "猿", "answers": [ "エン","さる","ましら" ]},
		{ "question": "獄", "answers": [ "ゴク","うったえる","ひとや" ]},
		{ "question": "獣", "answers": [ "ジュウ","けもの","けだもの","しし" ]},
		{ "question": "獲", "answers": [ "カク","える" ]},
		{ "question": "玄", "answers": [ "ゲン","くろ","くろい" ]},
		{ "question": "率", "answers": [ "リツ","ひきいる","ソツ","シュツ","スイ","おおむね","かしら","したがう","わりあい" ]},
		{ "question": "玉", "answers": [ "ギョク","たま","ゴク" ]},
		{ "question": "王", "answers": [ "オウ","きみ" ]},
		{ "question": "玩", "answers": [ "ガン","あじわう","もてあそぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "珍", "answers": [ "チン","めずらしい" ]},
		{ "question": "珠", "answers": [ "シュ","たま" ]},
		{ "question": "班", "answers": [ "ハン","かえす","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "現", "answers": [ "ゲン","あらわす","あらわれる","うつつ" ]},
		{ "question": "球", "answers": [ "キュウ","たま" ]},
		{ "question": "理", "answers": [ "リ","おさめる","ことわり","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "琴", "answers": [ "キン","こと","ゴン" ]},
		{ "question": "瑠", "answers": [ "ル" ]},
		{ "question": "璃", "answers": [ "リ" ]},
		{ "question": "璧", "answers": [ "ヘキ","たま" ]},
		{ "question": "環", "answers": [ "カン","たまき","めぐる","わ" ]},
		{ "question": "璽", "answers": [ "ジ","しるし" ]},
		{ "question": "瓦", "answers": [ "かわら","ガ","かわらけ","グラム" ]},
		{ "question": "瓶", "answers": [ "ビン","ヘイ","かめ" ]},
		{ "question": "甘", "answers": [ "カン","あまい","あまえる","あまやかす","うまい" ]},
		{ "question": "甚", "answers": [ "はなはだ","はなはだしい","ジン","いたく" ]},
		{ "question": "生", "answers": [ "ショウ","セイ","いかす","いきる","いける","うまれる","うむ","なま","はえる","はやす","おう","き","いのち","うぶ","なす","なる" ]},
		{ "question": "産", "answers": [ "サン","うまれる","うむ","うぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "用", "answers": [ "ヨウ","もちいる","はたらき","もって" ]},
		{ "question": "田", "answers": [ "デン","た","かり","かる" ]},
		{ "question": "由", "answers": [ "ユ","ユウ","ユイ","よし","なお","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "甲", "answers": [ "カン","コウ","かぶと","きのえ","つめ","よろい" ]},
		{ "question": "申", "answers": [ "もうす","シン","かさねる","さる" ]},
		{ "question": "男", "answers": [ "ダン","ナン","おとこ","おのこ" ]},
		{ "question": "町", "answers": [ "チョウ","まち","テイ","あぜみち" ]},
		{ "question": "画", "answers": [ "ガ","カク","え","えがく","かぎる","かく","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "界", "answers": [ "カイ","さかい" ]},
		{ "question": "畏", "answers": [ "イ","おそれる","かしこい","かしこまる" ]},
		{ "question": "畑", "answers": [ "はた","はたけ" ]},
		{ "question": "畔", "answers": [ "ハン","あぜ","くろ","そむく","ほとり" ]},
		{ "question": "留", "answers": [ "リュウ","ル","とまる","とめる","とどまる","とどめる" ]},
		{ "question": "畜", "answers": [ "チク","キク","かう","たくわえる","やしなう" ]},
		{ "question": "畝", "answers": [ "うね","ホ","ボウ","せ" ]},
		{ "question": "略", "answers": [ "リャク","おかす","おさめる","はかりごと","はかる","はぶく","ほぼ" ]},
		{ "question": "番", "answers": [ "バン","ハ","ハン","つがい","つがう","つがえる" ]},
		{ "question": "異", "answers": [ "イ","こと","あやしい" ]},
		{ "question": "畳", "answers": [ "ジョウ","たたみ","たたむ","チョウ","かさなる","かさねる" ]},
		{ "question": "畿", "answers": [ "キ","みやこ" ]},
		{ "question": "疎", "answers": [ "ソ","うとい","うとむ","ショ","うろ","おろ","おろか","おろそか","とおす","とおる","まばら" ]},
		{ "question": "疑", "answers": [ "ギ","うたがう","うたぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "疫", "answers": [ "エキ","ヤク" ]},
		{ "question": "疲", "answers": [ "ヒ","つかれる","つからす" ]},
		{ "question": "疾", "answers": [ "シツ","とく","とし","にくむ","はやい","やまい","やましい","やむ" ]},
		{ "question": "病", "answers": [ "ビョウ","やまい","やむ","ヘイ" ]},
		{ "question": "症", "answers": [ "ショウ","しるし" ]},
		{ "question": "痕", "answers": [ "コン","あと" ]},
		{ "question": "痘", "answers": [ "トウ","もがさ" ]},
		{ "question": "痛", "answers": [ "ツウ","いたい","いたむ","いためる","トウ","いたわしい","やめる" ]},
		{ "question": "痢", "answers": [ "リ" ]},
		{ "question": "痩", "answers": [ "やせる","ソウ","シュウ","こける","ほそい" ]},
		{ "question": "痴", "answers": [ "チ","おこ","おろか","しれる" ]},
		{ "question": "瘍", "answers": [ "ヨウ","かさ","できもの" ]},
		{ "question": "療", "answers": [ "リョウ","いやす" ]},
		{ "question": "癒", "answers": [ "ユ","いえる","いやす" ]},
		{ "question": "癖", "answers": [ "ヘキ","くせ" ]},
		{ "question": "発", "answers": [ "ハツ","ホツ","あばく","たつ","はなつ","ひらく" ]},
		{ "question": "登", "answers": [ "ト","トウ","のぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "白", "answers": [ "ハク","しら","しろ","しろい","ビャク","あきらか","せりふ","もうす" ]},
		{ "question": "百", "answers": [ "ヒャク","ハク","もも" ]},
		{ "question": "的", "answers": [ "テキ","まと","あきらか" ]},
		{ "question": "皆", "answers": [ "カイ","みな" ]},
		{ "question": "皇", "answers": [ "オウ","コウ","きみ","すめらぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "皮", "answers": [ "ヒ","かわ" ]},
		{ "question": "皿", "answers": [ "さら","ベイ" ]},
		{ "question": "盆", "answers": [ "ボン","ホン","はち" ]},
		{ "question": "益", "answers": [ "エキ","ヤク","ます","ますます" ]},
		{ "question": "盗", "answers": [ "トウ","ぬすむ","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "盛", "answers": [ "もる","セイ","さかる","さかん","ジョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "盟", "answers": [ "メイ","ちかう" ]},
		{ "question": "監", "answers": [ "カン","ケン","かんがみる","しらべる","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "盤", "answers": [ "バン","ハン","おおざら","まがる","めぐる","わだかまる" ]},
		{ "question": "目", "answers": [ "モク","め","ボク","ま","かなめ","まなこ" ]},
		{ "question": "盲", "answers": [ "モウ","ボウ","くらい","めくら" ]},
		{ "question": "直", "answers": [ "ジキ","チョク","ただちに","なおす","なおる","チ","あたい","じか","すぐ","ひた" ]},
		{ "question": "相", "answers": [ "ソウ","あい","ショウ","ありさま","さが","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "盾", "answers": [ "ジュン","たて" ]},
		{ "question": "省", "answers": [ "ショウ","セイ","はぶく","かえりみる" ]},
		{ "question": "眉", "answers": [ "ミ","まゆ","ビ","としより","ふち" ]},
		{ "question": "看", "answers": [ "カン","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "県", "answers": [ "ケン","あがた" ]},
		{ "question": "真", "answers": [ "シン","ま","まこと" ]},
		{ "question": "眠", "answers": [ "ミン","ねむい","ねむる","ベン" ]},
		{ "question": "眺", "answers": [ "チョウ","ながめる" ]},
		{ "question": "眼", "answers": [ "ガン","まなこ","ゲン","め" ]},
		{ "question": "着", "answers": [ "チャク","きせる","きる","つく","つける","ジャク" ]},
		{ "question": "睡", "answers": [ "スイ","ねむる" ]},
		{ "question": "督", "answers": [ "トク","うながす","かしら","ただす","ひきいる","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "睦", "answers": [ "ボク","モク","むつぶ","むつまじい","むつむ" ]},
		{ "question": "瞬", "answers": [ "シュン","またたく","しばたく","しばたたく","まじろぐ","まばたく" ]},
		{ "question": "瞭", "answers": [ "リョウ","あきらか" ]},
		{ "question": "瞳", "answers": [ "ドウ","ひとみ","トウ" ]},
		{ "question": "矛", "answers": [ "ム","ほこ","ボウ" ]},
		{ "question": "矢", "answers": [ "や","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "知", "answers": [ "チ","しる","しらせる" ]},
		{ "question": "短", "answers": [ "タン","みじかい" ]},
		{ "question": "矯", "answers": [ "キョウ","ためる","いつわる" ]},
		{ "question": "石", "answers": [ "シャク","セキ","いし","コク","ジャク" ]},
		{ "question": "砂", "answers": [ "サ","すな","シャ","いさご" ]},
		{ "question": "研", "answers": [ "ケン","とぐ","ゲン","みがく" ]},
		{ "question": "砕", "answers": [ "サイ","くだく","くだける" ]},
		{ "question": "砲", "answers": [ "ホウ","おおづつ","つつ" ]},
		{ "question": "破", "answers": [ "ハ","やぶる","やぶれる","われる" ]},
		{ "question": "硝", "answers": [ "ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "硫", "answers": [ "リュウ","ル" ]},
		{ "question": "硬", "answers": [ "コウ","かたい" ]},
		{ "question": "碁", "answers": [ "ゴ","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "碑", "answers": [ "ヒ","いしぶみ" ]},
		{ "question": "確", "answers": [ "カク","たしか","たしかめる","かたい","しかと","しっかり" ]},
		{ "question": "磁", "answers": [ "ジ","シ","やきもの" ]},
		{ "question": "磨", "answers": [ "マ","みがく","バ","する","とぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "礁", "answers": [ "ショウ","かくれいわ" ]},
		{ "question": "礎", "answers": [ "ソ","いしずえ" ]},
		{ "question": "示", "answers": [ "ジ","しめす","シ","キ","ギ" ]},
		{ "question": "礼", "answers": [ "レイ","ライ","うやまう","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "社", "answers": [ "シャ","やしろ","ジャ" ]},
		{ "question": "祈", "answers": [ "キ","いのる" ]},
		{ "question": "祉", "answers": [ "シ","さいわい" ]},
		{ "question": "祖", "answers": [ "ソ","おや","じじ","はじめ" ]},
		{ "question": "祝", "answers": [ "シュク","いわう","シュウ","たつ","のる","のろう" ]},
		{ "question": "神", "answers": [ "シン","ジン","かみ","かん","こう","たましい" ]},
		{ "question": "祥", "answers": [ "ショウ","きざし","さいわい","さち" ]},
		{ "question": "票", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","ふだ" ]},
		{ "question": "祭", "answers": [ "サイ","まつり","まつる" ]},
		{ "question": "禁", "answers": [ "キン","いさめる","いむ","とどめる" ]},
		{ "question": "禅", "answers": [ "ゼン","セン","ゆずる" ]},
		{ "question": "禍", "answers": [ "カ","まが","わざわい" ]},
		{ "question": "福", "answers": [ "フク","さいわい" ]},
		{ "question": "秀", "answers": [ "シュウ","ひいでる" ]},
		{ "question": "私", "answers": [ "シ","わたくし","わたし","ひそか" ]},
		{ "question": "秋", "answers": [ "シュウ","あき","とき" ]},
		{ "question": "科", "answers": [ "カ","しぐさ","しな","とが" ]},
		{ "question": "秒", "answers": [ "ビョウ","のぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "秘", "answers": [ "ヒ","ひめる","かくす","ひそか" ]},
		{ "question": "租", "answers": [ "ソ","ちんがり","みつぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "秩", "answers": [ "チツ","ついで","ふち" ]},
		{ "question": "称", "answers": [ "ショウ","あげる","かなう","たたえる","となえる","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "移", "answers": [ "イ","うつす","うつる" ]},
		{ "question": "程", "answers": [ "テイ","ほど","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "税", "answers": [ "ゼイ","セイ","みつぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "稚", "answers": [ "チ","いとけない","わかい" ]},
		{ "question": "種", "answers": [ "シュ","たね","ショウ","うえる","くさ" ]},
		{ "question": "稲", "answers": [ "トウ","いな","いね" ]},
		{ "question": "稼", "answers": [ "かせぐ","カ","うえる","みのり" ]},
		{ "question": "稽", "answers": [ "ケイ","かんがえる","とどこおる","とどめる" ]},
		{ "question": "稿", "answers": [ "コウ","したがき","わら" ]},
		{ "question": "穀", "answers": [ "コク" ]},
		{ "question": "穂", "answers": [ "ほ","スイ" ]},
		{ "question": "積", "answers": [ "セキ","つむ","つもる","シ","シャク","たくわえる" ]},
		{ "question": "穏", "answers": [ "オン","おだやか","やすらか" ]},
		{ "question": "穫", "answers": [ "カク","かる","とりいれる" ]},
		{ "question": "穴", "answers": [ "あな","ケツ" ]},
		{ "question": "究", "answers": [ "キュウ","きわめる","ク","きわまる" ]},
		{ "question": "空", "answers": [ "クウ","あく","あける","から","そら","あな","うつける","うつろ","うろ","すく","むなしい" ]},
		{ "question": "突", "answers": [ "トツ","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "窃", "answers": [ "セツ","ぬすむ","ひそかに" ]},
		{ "question": "窒", "answers": [ "チツ","ふさがる" ]},
		{ "question": "窓", "answers": [ "ソウ","まど" ]},
		{ "question": "窟", "answers": [ "クツ","いわや","ほらあな" ]},
		{ "question": "窮", "answers": [ "キュウ","きわまる","きわめる" ]},
		{ "question": "窯", "answers": [ "かま","ヨウ" ]},
		{ "question": "立", "answers": [ "リツ","たつ","たてる","リュウ","リットル" ]},
		{ "question": "竜", "answers": [ "リュウ","たつ","リョウ","リン" ]},
		{ "question": "章", "answers": [ "ショウ","あや","しるし","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "童", "answers": [ "ドウ","わらべ","トウ","わらわ" ]},
		{ "question": "端", "answers": [ "タン","はし","はた","は","ただしい","はした","はじめ","はな" ]},
		{ "question": "競", "answers": [ "キョウ","ケイ","きそう","せる","きおう","くらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "竹", "answers": [ "チク","たけ","シツ" ]},
		{ "question": "笑", "answers": [ "わらう","ショウ","えむ" ]},
		{ "question": "笛", "answers": [ "テキ","ふえ","ジャク" ]},
		{ "question": "符", "answers": [ "フ","わりふ" ]},
		{ "question": "第", "answers": [ "ダイ","テイ","ついで","やしき" ]},
		{ "question": "筆", "answers": [ "ヒツ","ふで" ]},
		{ "question": "等", "answers": [ "トウ","ひとしい","など","ら" ]},
		{ "question": "筋", "answers": [ "キン","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "筒", "answers": [ "トウ","つつ" ]},
		{ "question": "答", "answers": [ "トウ","こたえ","こたえる" ]},
		{ "question": "策", "answers": [ "サク","つえ","はかりごと","ふだ","むち" ]},
		{ "question": "箇", "answers": [ "カ","コ" ]},
		{ "question": "箋", "answers": [ "セン","かきもの","てがみ","ときあかし","なふだ","はりふだ","ふだ" ]},
		{ "question": "算", "answers": [ "サン","かず","かぞえる" ]},
		{ "question": "管", "answers": [ "カン","くだ","つかさどる","ふえ" ]},
		{ "question": "箱", "answers": [ "はこ","ショウ","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "箸", "answers": [ "はし","チョ" ]},
		{ "question": "節", "answers": [ "セツ","ふし","セチ","ノット","みさお" ]},
		{ "question": "範", "answers": [ "ハン","いがた","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "築", "answers": [ "チク","きずく","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "篤", "answers": [ "トク","あつい" ]},
		{ "question": "簡", "answers": [ "カン","ケン","えらぶ","ふだ" ]},
		{ "question": "簿", "answers": [ "ボ","ハク","バク","ホ" ]},
		{ "question": "籍", "answers": [ "セキ","シャ","ジャク","しく","ふみ","ふむ" ]},
		{ "question": "籠", "answers": [ "かご","こもる","ロウ","ル","こめる" ]},
		{ "question": "米", "answers": [ "ベイ","マイ","こめ","メ","メトル","よね" ]},
		{ "question": "粉", "answers": [ "フン","こ","こな","デシメトル" ]},
		{ "question": "粋", "answers": [ "スイ","いき" ]},
		{ "question": "粒", "answers": [ "リュウ","つぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "粗", "answers": [ "ソ","あらい","ほぼ" ]},
		{ "question": "粘", "answers": [ "ネン","ねばる","デン" ]},
		{ "question": "粛", "answers": [ "シュク","つつしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "粧", "answers": [ "ショウ","ソウ","めかす","よそおう" ]},
		{ "question": "精", "answers": [ "セイ","ショウ","くわしい","しらげる","もののけ" ]},
		{ "question": "糖", "answers": [ "トウ","あめ" ]},
		{ "question": "糧", "answers": [ "リョウ","ロウ","かて" ]},
		{ "question": "糸", "answers": [ "シ","いと","ベキ" ]},
		{ "question": "系", "answers": [ "ケイ","すじ","つなぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "糾", "answers": [ "キュウ","あざなう","ただす" ]},
		{ "question": "紀", "answers": [ "キ","おさめる","しるす","のり" ]},
		{ "question": "約", "answers": [ "ヤク","ちかう","つづまやか","つづめる","つましい" ]},
		{ "question": "紅", "answers": [ "コウ","べに","ク","くれない","グ","あかい","もみ" ]},
		{ "question": "紋", "answers": [ "モン","ブン","あや" ]},
		{ "question": "納", "answers": [ "ノウ","おさまる","おさめる","トウ","ナッ","ナ","ナン","いれる" ]},
		{ "question": "純", "answers": [ "ジュン","トン","きいと" ]},
		{ "question": "紙", "answers": [ "シ","かみ" ]},
		{ "question": "級", "answers": [ "キュウ","くび","しな" ]},
		{ "question": "紛", "answers": [ "フン","まぎらす","まぎらわしい","まぎらわす","まぎれる","まがう","まぐれ","みだれる" ]},
		{ "question": "素", "answers": [ "ソ","ス","しろい","もと","もとより" ]},
		{ "question": "紡", "answers": [ "ボウ","つむぐ","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "索", "answers": [ "サク","さがす","つな","なわ","もとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "紫", "answers": [ "シ","むらさき" ]},
		{ "question": "累", "answers": [ "ルイ","かさなる","かさねる","しきりに","しばる","わずらわす" ]},
		{ "question": "細", "answers": [ "サイ","こまか","こまかい","ほそい","ほそる","くわしい","ささやか" ]},
		{ "question": "紳", "answers": [ "シン","おおおび" ]},
		{ "question": "紹", "answers": [ "ショウ","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "紺", "answers": [ "コン" ]},
		{ "question": "終", "answers": [ "シュウ","おえる","おわる","しまう","ついに" ]},
		{ "question": "組", "answers": [ "ソ","くみ","くむ","くみひも" ]},
		{ "question": "経", "answers": [ "ケイ","へる","キョウ","キン","おさめる","たつ","たていと" ]},
		{ "question": "結", "answers": [ "ケツ","むすぶ","ゆう","ゆわえる","ケイ","ケチ","すく" ]},
		{ "question": "絞", "answers": [ "しぼる","しまる","しめる","コウ","くびる" ]},
		{ "question": "絡", "answers": [ "ラク","からまる","からむ","からめる","からげる","つなぐ","まとう" ]},
		{ "question": "給", "answers": [ "キュウ","たまう","たまわる" ]},
		{ "question": "統", "answers": [ "トウ","すべる","おさめる","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "絵", "answers": [ "エ","カイ","えがく" ]},
		{ "question": "絶", "answers": [ "ゼツ","たえる","たつ","たやす","ゼチ","セツ","はなはだ","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "絹", "answers": [ "きぬ","ケン" ]},
		{ "question": "継", "answers": [ "ケイ","つぐ","まま" ]},
		{ "question": "続", "answers": [ "ゾク","つづく","つづける","ショク","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "維", "answers": [ "イ","これ","つなぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "綱", "answers": [ "コウ","つな" ]},
		{ "question": "網", "answers": [ "モウ","あみ","ボウ" ]},
		{ "question": "綻", "answers": [ "タン","ほころびる","ほころぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "綿", "answers": [ "メン","わた","ベン","つらなる" ]},
		{ "question": "緊", "answers": [ "キン","かたい","きびしい","しめる","ちぢむ" ]},
		{ "question": "総", "answers": [ "ソウ","すべて","すべる","ふさ" ]},
		{ "question": "緑", "answers": [ "リョク","みどり","ロク" ]},
		{ "question": "緒", "answers": [ "ショ","チョ","お","いとぐち" ]},
		{ "question": "線", "answers": [ "セン","いと","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "締", "answers": [ "テイ","しまる","しめる","むすぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "編", "answers": [ "ヘン","あむ","とじいと","ふみ" ]},
		{ "question": "緩", "answers": [ "カン","ゆるい","ゆるむ","ゆるめる","ゆるやか","ぬるい" ]},
		{ "question": "緯", "answers": [ "イ","ぬき","よこいと" ]},
		{ "question": "練", "answers": [ "レン","ねる","ねりぎぬ" ]},
		{ "question": "緻", "answers": [ "チ","こまかい" ]},
		{ "question": "縁", "answers": [ "エン","ふち","えにし","へり","ゆかり","よすが","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "縄", "answers": [ "ジョウ","なわ","ただす" ]},
		{ "question": "縛", "answers": [ "バク","しばる","ハク","いましめる" ]},
		{ "question": "縦", "answers": [ "ジュウ","たて","ショウ","はなつ","ほしいまま","ゆるす","ゆるめる","よしんば" ]},
		{ "question": "縫", "answers": [ "ホウ","ぬう" ]},
		{ "question": "縮", "answers": [ "シュク","ちぢまる","ちぢむ","ちぢめる","ちぢらす","ちぢれる" ]},
		{ "question": "績", "answers": [ "セキ","いさお","うむ","つむぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "繁", "answers": [ "ハン","しげる","わずらわしい" ]},
		{ "question": "繊", "answers": [ "セン","チン","しなやか","ちいさい","ほそい" ]},
		{ "question": "織", "answers": [ "シキ","おる","ショク","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "繕", "answers": [ "ゼン","つくろう","セン" ]},
		{ "question": "繭", "answers": [ "まゆ","ケン" ]},
		{ "question": "繰", "answers": [ "くる","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "缶", "answers": [ "カン","フ","かま","ほとぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "罪", "answers": [ "ザイ","つみ" ]},
		{ "question": "置", "answers": [ "チ","おく" ]},
		{ "question": "罰", "answers": [ "バチ","バツ","ハツ" ]},
		{ "question": "署", "answers": [ "ショ","しるす","やくわり" ]},
		{ "question": "罵", "answers": [ "バ","ののしる" ]},
		{ "question": "罷", "answers": [ "ヒ","つかれる","まかる","やめる" ]},
		{ "question": "羅", "answers": [ "ラ","あみ","うすぎぬ","つらなる" ]},
		{ "question": "羊", "answers": [ "ヨウ","ひつじ" ]},
		{ "question": "美", "answers": [ "ビ","うつくしい","ミ","ほめる","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "羞", "answers": [ "シュウ","すすめる","はじ","はじる","はずかしめ","はずかしめる" ]},
		{ "question": "群", "answers": [ "グン","むら","むれ","むれる" ]},
		{ "question": "羨", "answers": [ "うらやましい","うらやむ","セン","エン","ゼン","あまる","はかみち" ]},
		{ "question": "義", "answers": [ "ギ","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "羽", "answers": [ "は","はね","ウ" ]},
		{ "question": "翁", "answers": [ "オウ","おきな" ]},
		{ "question": "翌", "answers": [ "ヨク" ]},
		{ "question": "習", "answers": [ "シュウ","ならう","ジュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "翻", "answers": [ "ホン","ひるがえす","ひるがえる","ハン" ]},
		{ "question": "翼", "answers": [ "ヨク","つばさ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "老", "answers": [ "ロウ","おいる","ふける" ]},
		{ "question": "考", "answers": [ "コウ","かんがえる" ]},
		{ "question": "者", "answers": [ "シャ","もの" ]},
		{ "question": "耐", "answers": [ "タイ","たえる","ダイ","ドウ","ナイ","ノウ" ]},
		{ "question": "耕", "answers": [ "コウ","たがやす" ]},
		{ "question": "耗", "answers": [ "モウ","コウ","ボウ","たより","へる" ]},
		{ "question": "耳", "answers": [ "みみ","ジ","ニ","のみ" ]},
		{ "question": "聖", "answers": [ "セイ","ショウ","ひじり" ]},
		{ "question": "聞", "answers": [ "ブン","きく","きこえる","モン" ]},
		{ "question": "聴", "answers": [ "チョウ","きく","テイ","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "職", "answers": [ "ショク","シキ","トク","つかさ","つかさどる","つとめ" ]},
		{ "question": "肉", "answers": [ "ニク","ジク","しし" ]},
		{ "question": "肌", "answers": [ "はだ","キ","はだえ" ]},
		{ "question": "肖", "answers": [ "ショウ","あやかる","かたどる","にる" ]},
		{ "question": "肘", "answers": [ "ひじ","チュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "肝", "answers": [ "カン","きも" ]},
		{ "question": "股", "answers": [ "コ","また","もも" ]},
		{ "question": "肢", "answers": [ "シ","てあし" ]},
		{ "question": "肥", "answers": [ "ヒ","こえ","こえる","こやし","こやす","ふとる" ]},
		{ "question": "肩", "answers": [ "かた","ケン" ]},
		{ "question": "肪", "answers": [ "ボウ","ホウ","あぶら" ]},
		{ "question": "肯", "answers": [ "コウ","あえて","うなずく","うべなう","がえんじる" ]},
		{ "question": "育", "answers": [ "イク","そだつ","そだてる","はぐくむ" ]},
		{ "question": "肺", "answers": [ "ハイ" ]},
		{ "question": "胃", "answers": [ "イ" ]},
		{ "question": "胆", "answers": [ "タン","トウ","きも" ]},
		{ "question": "背", "answers": [ "ハイ","せ","せい","そむく","そむける","うしろ" ]},
		{ "question": "胎", "answers": [ "タイ","はらむ" ]},
		{ "question": "胞", "answers": [ "ホウ","はら" ]},
		{ "question": "胴", "answers": [ "ドウ","トウ" ]},
		{ "question": "胸", "answers": [ "キョウ","むね","むな","こころ" ]},
		{ "question": "能", "answers": [ "ノウ","ダイ","ドウ","あたう","はたらき","よく","よくする" ]},
		{ "question": "脂", "answers": [ "シ","あぶら","べに","やに" ]},
		{ "question": "脅", "answers": [ "キョウ","おどかす","おどす","おびやかす","おびえる" ]},
		{ "question": "脇", "answers": [ "わき","キョウ","かたわら" ]},
		{ "question": "脈", "answers": [ "ミャク","バク","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "脊", "answers": [ "セキ","せ","せい" ]},
		{ "question": "脚", "answers": [ "キャク","あし","キャ","カク" ]},
		{ "question": "脱", "answers": [ "ダツ","ぬぐ","ぬげる","タイ","タツ" ]},
		{ "question": "脳", "answers": [ "ノウ","ドウ" ]},
		{ "question": "腎", "answers": [ "ジン","シン" ]},
		{ "question": "腐", "answers": [ "フ","くさらす","くさる","くされる","くさす" ]},
		{ "question": "腕", "answers": [ "ワン","うで","かいな" ]},
		{ "question": "腫", "answers": [ "シュ","はらす","はれる","ショウ","はれもの" ]},
		{ "question": "腰", "answers": [ "こし","ヨウ" ]},
		{ "question": "腸", "answers": [ "チョウ","はらわた","わた" ]},
		{ "question": "腹", "answers": [ "フク","はら","こころ" ]},
		{ "question": "腺", "answers": [ "セン","すじ" ]},
		{ "question": "膚", "answers": [ "フ","はだ","はだえ" ]},
		{ "question": "膜", "answers": [ "マク","バク","ボ","モ" ]},
		{ "question": "膝", "answers": [ "ひざ","シツ" ]},
		{ "question": "膨", "answers": [ "ボウ","ふくらむ","ふくれる","ホウ","ふくよか" ]},
		{ "question": "膳", "answers": [ "ゼン","セン","かしわ","そなえる" ]},
		{ "question": "臆", "answers": [ "オク","おしはかる" ]},
		{ "question": "臓", "answers": [ "ゾウ","ソウ","はらわた" ]},
		{ "question": "臣", "answers": [ "シン","ジン","おみ" ]},
		{ "question": "臨", "answers": [ "リン","のぞむ" ]},
		{ "question": "自", "answers": [ "シ","ジ","みずから","おのずから","より" ]},
		{ "question": "臭", "answers": [ "シュウ","くさい","におう","キュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "至", "answers": [ "シ","いたる" ]},
		{ "question": "致", "answers": [ "チ","いたす" ]},
		{ "question": "臼", "answers": [ "キュウ","うす" ]},
		{ "question": "興", "answers": [ "キョウ","コウ","おこす","おこる" ]},
		{ "question": "舌", "answers": [ "した","ゼツ","セツ","ことば" ]},
		{ "question": "舎", "answers": [ "シャ","セキ","いえ","おく","やど","やどる" ]},
		{ "question": "舗", "answers": [ "ホ","フ","しく","みせ" ]},
		{ "question": "舞", "answers": [ "ブ","まい","まう","ム","もてあそぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "舟", "answers": [ "シュウ","ふな","ふね","シュ" ]},
		{ "question": "航", "answers": [ "コウ","わたる" ]},
		{ "question": "般", "answers": [ "ハン","たぐい","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "舶", "answers": [ "ハク","おおぶね" ]},
		{ "question": "舷", "answers": [ "ゲン","ふなばた","ふなべり" ]},
		{ "question": "船", "answers": [ "セン","ふな","ふね" ]},
		{ "question": "艇", "answers": [ "テイ","こぶね" ]},
		{ "question": "艦", "answers": [ "カン","いくさぶね" ]},
		{ "question": "良", "answers": [ "リョウ","よい","やや" ]},
		{ "question": "色", "answers": [ "シキ","ショク","いろ" ]},
		{ "question": "艶", "answers": [ "つや","エン","あでやか","うらやむ","なまめかしい" ]},
		{ "question": "芋", "answers": [ "いも","ウ" ]},
		{ "question": "芝", "answers": [ "しば","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "芯", "answers": [ "シン","とうしんぐさ" ]},
		{ "question": "花", "answers": [ "カ","はな","ケ" ]},
		{ "question": "芳", "answers": [ "ホウ","かんばしい","かおり","かぐわしい" ]},
		{ "question": "芸", "answers": [ "ゲイ","ウン","うえる","くさぎる","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "芽", "answers": [ "ガ","め","めぐむ" ]},
		{ "question": "苗", "answers": [ "なえ","なわ","ビョウ","ミョウ","かり" ]},
		{ "question": "苛", "answers": [ "カ","いじめる","いらだつ","からい","きびしい","さいなむ","むごい","わずらわしい" ]},
		{ "question": "若", "answers": [ "わかい","ジャク","ニャク","もしくは","ジャ","ニャ","ごとし","しく","なんじ","もし" ]},
		{ "question": "苦", "answers": [ "ク","くるしい","くるしむ","くるしめる","にがい","にがる","にがな","はなはだ" ]},
		{ "question": "英", "answers": [ "エイ","はな","はなぶさ","ひいでる" ]},
		{ "question": "茂", "answers": [ "モ","しげる","ボウ","すぐれる" ]},
		{ "question": "茎", "answers": [ "ケイ","くき","なかご" ]},
		{ "question": "茨", "answers": [ "いばら","シ","くさぶき" ]},
		{ "question": "茶", "answers": [ "チャ","サ" ]},
		{ "question": "草", "answers": [ "ソウ","くさ" ]},
		{ "question": "荒", "answers": [ "コウ","あらい","あらす","あれる","すさぶ","すさむ" ]},
		{ "question": "荘", "answers": [ "ソウ","ショウ","おごそか","しもやしき" ]},
		{ "question": "荷", "answers": [ "に","カ","になう","はす" ]},
		{ "question": "菊", "answers": [ "キク" ]},
		{ "question": "菌", "answers": [ "キン","きのこ","たけ" ]},
		{ "question": "菓", "answers": [ "カ","くだもの" ]},
		{ "question": "菜", "answers": [ "サイ","な" ]},
		{ "question": "華", "answers": [ "カ","はな","ケ","ゲ","しろい" ]},
		{ "question": "萎", "answers": [ "イ","なえる","しおれる","しなびる","しぼむ","つかれる" ]},
		{ "question": "落", "answers": [ "ラク","おちる","おとす","さと" ]},
		{ "question": "葉", "answers": [ "ヨウ","は","ショウ","かみ","すえ" ]},
		{ "question": "著", "answers": [ "チョ","あらわす","いちじるしい","ジャク","チャク","きる","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "葛", "answers": [ "カツ","くず","かずら","かたびら","つづら" ]},
		{ "question": "葬", "answers": [ "ソウ","ほうむる" ]},
		{ "question": "蒸", "answers": [ "ジョウ","むす","むらす","むれる","おおい","ふかす","ふける" ]},
		{ "question": "蓄", "answers": [ "チク","たくわえる" ]},
		{ "question": "蓋", "answers": [ "ガイ","ふた","コウ","おおい","おおう","かさ","けだし" ]},
		{ "question": "蔑", "answers": [ "ベツ","さげすむ","くらい","ないがしろ","なみする" ]},
		{ "question": "蔵", "answers": [ "ゾウ","くら","ソウ","おさめる","かくれる" ]},
		{ "question": "蔽", "answers": [ "ヘイ","おおい","おおう","くらい","さだめる" ]},
		{ "question": "薄", "answers": [ "ハク","うすい","うすまる","うすめる","うすらぐ","うすれる","すすき","せまる" ]},
		{ "question": "薦", "answers": [ "セン","すすめる","こも","しきりに","しく" ]},
		{ "question": "薪", "answers": [ "シン","たきぎ","まき" ]},
		{ "question": "薫", "answers": [ "かおる","クン","かおりぐさ","たく" ]},
		{ "question": "薬", "answers": [ "ヤク","くすり" ]},
		{ "question": "藍", "answers": [ "あい","ラン" ]},
		{ "question": "藤", "answers": [ "トウ","ふじ" ]},
		{ "question": "藩", "answers": [ "ハン","まがき" ]},
		{ "question": "藻", "answers": [ "ソウ","も","あや" ]},
		{ "question": "虎", "answers": [ "コ","とら" ]},
		{ "question": "虐", "answers": [ "ギャク","しいたげる","むごい" ]},
		{ "question": "虚", "answers": [ "キョ","コ","うつける","うつろ","うろ","むなしい" ]},
		{ "question": "虜", "answers": [ "リョ","ロ","えびす","しもべ","とりこ" ]},
		{ "question": "虞", "answers": [ "おそれ","グ" ]},
		{ "question": "虫", "answers": [ "チュウ","むし","キ" ]},
		{ "question": "虹", "answers": [ "にじ","コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "蚊", "answers": [ "か","ブン" ]},
		{ "question": "蚕", "answers": [ "サン","かいこ","テン","こ" ]},
		{ "question": "蛇", "answers": [ "ジャ","ダ","へび","イ","タ" ]},
		{ "question": "蛍", "answers": [ "ケイ","ほたる" ]},
		{ "question": "蛮", "answers": [ "バン","えびす" ]},
		{ "question": "蜂", "answers": [ "ホウ","はち","むらがる" ]},
		{ "question": "蜜", "answers": [ "ミツ","ビツ" ]},
		{ "question": "融", "answers": [ "ユウ","とおる","とける" ]},
		{ "question": "血", "answers": [ "ケツ","ち","ケチ" ]},
		{ "question": "衆", "answers": [ "シュウ","シュ","おおい" ]},
		{ "question": "行", "answers": [ "ギョウ","コウ","いく","おこなう","ゆく","アン","しぬ","みち","やる" ]},
		{ "question": "術", "answers": [ "ジュツ","シュツ","スイ","すべ","わざ" ]},
		{ "question": "街", "answers": [ "ガイ","まち","カイ","ちまた" ]},
		{ "question": "衛", "answers": [ "エイ","エ","まもる" ]},
		{ "question": "衝", "answers": [ "ショウ","つく" ]},
		{ "question": "衡", "answers": [ "コウ","くびき","はかり","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "衣", "answers": [ "イ","ころも","エ","きぬ","きる" ]},
		{ "question": "表", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","あらわす","あらわれる","おもて","しるし" ]},
		{ "question": "衰", "answers": [ "スイ","おとろえる","サイ","シ" ]},
		{ "question": "衷", "answers": [ "チュウ","うち","こころ","まこと" ]},
		{ "question": "袋", "answers": [ "ふくろ","タイ","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "袖", "answers": [ "そで","シュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "被", "answers": [ "ヒ","こうむる","おおう","かずける","かぶせる","かぶる" ]},
		{ "question": "裁", "answers": [ "サイ","さばく","たつ" ]},
		{ "question": "裂", "answers": [ "レツ","さく","さける","きれ" ]},
		{ "question": "装", "answers": [ "ソウ","ショウ","よそおう","よそう" ]},
		{ "question": "裏", "answers": [ "うら","リ","うち" ]},
		{ "question": "裕", "answers": [ "ユウ","ひろい","ゆたか" ]},
		{ "question": "補", "answers": [ "ホ","おぎなう","フ","たすける" ]},
		{ "question": "裸", "answers": [ "ラ","はだか" ]},
		{ "question": "製", "answers": [ "セイ","つくる" ]},
		{ "question": "裾", "answers": [ "すそ","キョ" ]},
		{ "question": "複", "answers": [ "フク","かさねる" ]},
		{ "question": "褐", "answers": [ "カツ","ぬのこ" ]},
		{ "question": "褒", "answers": [ "ほめる","ホウ" ]},
		{ "question": "襟", "answers": [ "えり","キン","むね" ]},
		{ "question": "襲", "answers": [ "シュウ","おそう","かさね","かさねる","つぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "西", "answers": [ "サイ","セイ","にし","スイ" ]},
		{ "question": "要", "answers": [ "ヨウ","かなめ","いる","もとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "覆", "answers": [ "フク","おおう","くつがえす","くつがえる","フ","フウ" ]},
		{ "question": "覇", "answers": [ "ハ","ハク","はたがしら" ]},
		{ "question": "見", "answers": [ "ケン","みえる","みせる","みる","ゲン","あらわす","あらわれる","まみえる" ]},
		{ "question": "規", "answers": [ "キ","ただす","のり","ぶんまわし" ]},
		{ "question": "視", "answers": [ "シ","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "覚", "answers": [ "カク","おぼえる","さます","さめる","コウ","さとり","さとる" ]},
		{ "question": "覧", "answers": [ "ラン","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "親", "answers": [ "シン","おや","したしい","したしむ","みずから" ]},
		{ "question": "観", "answers": [ "カン","しめす","みる","みせる" ]},
		{ "question": "角", "answers": [ "カク","かど","つの","ロク","くらべる","すみ" ]},
		{ "question": "解", "answers": [ "カイ","とかす","とく","とける","ゲ","さとる","ほぐれる","ほつれる","ほどく","ほどける","わかる" ]},
		{ "question": "触", "answers": [ "ショク","さわる","ふれる","ソク" ]},
		{ "question": "言", "answers": [ "ゲン","ゴン","いう","こと","ギン","ことば" ]},
		{ "question": "訂", "answers": [ "テイ","さだめる","ただす" ]},
		{ "question": "訃", "answers": [ "フ","しらせ","つげる" ]},
		{ "question": "計", "answers": [ "ケイ","はからう","はかる","かぞえる" ]},
		{ "question": "討", "answers": [ "トウ","うつ","たずねる" ]},
		{ "question": "訓", "answers": [ "クン","キン","おしえる","よむ" ]},
		{ "question": "託", "answers": [ "タク","かこつ","かこつける","ことづかる","まかせる" ]},
		{ "question": "記", "answers": [ "キ","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "訟", "answers": [ "ショウ","ジュ","うったえ","うったえる" ]},
		{ "question": "訪", "answers": [ "ホウ","たずねる","おとずれる","おとなう","とう" ]},
		{ "question": "設", "answers": [ "セツ","もうける","セチ","しつらえる","たとい","もし" ]},
		{ "question": "許", "answers": [ "キョ","ゆるす","コ","ばかり","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "訳", "answers": [ "ヤク","わけ","エキ","とく" ]},
		{ "question": "訴", "answers": [ "ソ","うったえる" ]},
		{ "question": "診", "answers": [ "シン","みる" ]},
		{ "question": "証", "answers": [ "ショウ","あかし","あかす" ]},
		{ "question": "詐", "answers": [ "サ","あざむく","いつわり","いつわる" ]},
		{ "question": "詔", "answers": [ "ショウ","みことのり","つげる" ]},
		{ "question": "評", "answers": [ "ヒョウ","ヘイ","あげつらう","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "詞", "answers": [ "シ","ことば" ]},
		{ "question": "詠", "answers": [ "エイ","よむ","うたう","ながめる" ]},
		{ "question": "詣", "answers": [ "もうでる","ケイ","いたる","まいる" ]},
		{ "question": "試", "answers": [ "シ","こころみる","ためす" ]},
		{ "question": "詩", "answers": [ "シ","うた" ]},
		{ "question": "詮", "answers": [ "セン","あきらか","えらぶ","しらべる","そなわる" ]},
		{ "question": "詰", "answers": [ "つまる","つむ","つめる","キツ","なじる" ]},
		{ "question": "話", "answers": [ "ワ","はなし","はなす" ]},
		{ "question": "該", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","かねる","そなわる","その" ]},
		{ "question": "詳", "answers": [ "ショウ","くわしい","ヨウ","つまびらか" ]},
		{ "question": "誇", "answers": [ "コ","ほこる" ]},
		{ "question": "誉", "answers": [ "ヨ","ほまれ","ほめる" ]},
		{ "question": "誌", "answers": [ "シ","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "認", "answers": [ "みとめる","ニン","ジン","したためる" ]},
		{ "question": "誓", "answers": [ "セイ","ちかう","ゼイ" ]},
		{ "question": "誕", "answers": [ "タン","いつわる","うまれる","ほしいまま" ]},
		{ "question": "誘", "answers": [ "ユウ","さそう","いざなう","おびく" ]},
		{ "question": "語", "answers": [ "ゴ","かたらう","かたる","ギョ","ことば","つげる" ]},
		{ "question": "誠", "answers": [ "セイ","まこと","ジョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "誤", "answers": [ "ゴ","あやまる","まどわす" ]},
		{ "question": "説", "answers": [ "セツ","とく","ゼイ","エツ","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "読", "answers": [ "トウ","トク","ドク","よむ" ]},
		{ "question": "誰", "answers": [ "だれ","スイ","た","たれ" ]},
		{ "question": "課", "answers": [ "カ","こころみる","はかる","わりあてる" ]},
		{ "question": "調", "answers": [ "チョウ","しらべる","ととのう","ととのえる","あざける","みつぎ","やわらぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "談", "answers": [ "ダン","タン","かたる" ]},
		{ "question": "請", "answers": [ "セイ","うける","シン","こう","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "論", "answers": [ "ロン","あげつらう","とく" ]},
		{ "question": "諦", "answers": [ "テイ","あきらめる","タイ","つまびらか","まこと" ]},
		{ "question": "諧", "answers": [ "カイ","かなう","たわむれ","ととのう","やわらぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "諭", "answers": [ "ユ","さとす" ]},
		{ "question": "諮", "answers": [ "シ","はかる","とう" ]},
		{ "question": "諸", "answers": [ "ショ","もろ","もろもろ" ]},
		{ "question": "諾", "answers": [ "ダク","うべなう" ]},
		{ "question": "謀", "answers": [ "ボウ","ム","はかる","はかりごと" ]},
		{ "question": "謁", "answers": [ "エツ","まみえる" ]},
		{ "question": "謄", "answers": [ "トウ","うつす" ]},
		{ "question": "謎", "answers": [ "なぞ","ベイ","メイ" ]},
		{ "question": "謙", "answers": [ "ケン","へりくだる" ]},
		{ "question": "講", "answers": [ "コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "謝", "answers": [ "シャ","あやまる","ことわる","さる" ]},
		{ "question": "謡", "answers": [ "ヨウ","うたい","うたう" ]},
		{ "question": "謹", "answers": [ "キン","つつしむ" ]},
		{ "question": "識", "answers": [ "シキ","シ","ショク","しる","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "譜", "answers": [ "フ","しるす","つづく" ]},
		{ "question": "警", "answers": [ "ケイ","キョウ","いましめる" ]},
		{ "question": "議", "answers": [ "ギ","はかる" ]},
		{ "question": "譲", "answers": [ "ジョウ","ゆずる","せめる" ]},
		{ "question": "護", "answers": [ "ゴ","まもり","まもる" ]},
		{ "question": "谷", "answers": [ "たに","コク","ロク","きわまる","や" ]},
		{ "question": "豆", "answers": [ "ズ","トウ","まめ","たかつき" ]},
		{ "question": "豊", "answers": [ "ホウ","ゆたか","とよ" ]},
		{ "question": "豚", "answers": [ "トン","ぶた" ]},
		{ "question": "象", "answers": [ "ショウ","ゾウ","かたち","かたどる" ]},
		{ "question": "豪", "answers": [ "ゴウ","コウ","えらい","つよい" ]},
		{ "question": "貌", "answers": [ "ボウ","バク","かお","かたち" ]},
		{ "question": "貝", "answers": [ "かい","バイ" ]},
		{ "question": "貞", "answers": [ "テイ","ジョウ","ただしい" ]},
		{ "question": "負", "answers": [ "フ","おう","まかす","まける","ブ","フウ","そむく","たのむ" ]},
		{ "question": "財", "answers": [ "ザイ","サイ","たから" ]},
		{ "question": "貢", "answers": [ "コウ","ク","みつぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "貧", "answers": [ "ビン","まずしい","ヒン" ]},
		{ "question": "貨", "answers": [ "カ","たから" ]},
		{ "question": "販", "answers": [ "ハン","あきなう","ひさぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "貪", "answers": [ "ドン","むさぼる","タン" ]},
		{ "question": "貫", "answers": [ "カン","つらぬく","ワン","ぬき","ぬく","ひく" ]},
		{ "question": "責", "answers": [ "セキ","せめる","サイ","シャク" ]},
		{ "question": "貯", "answers": [ "チョ","たくわえる" ]},
		{ "question": "貴", "answers": [ "キ","たっとい","たっとぶ","とうとい","とうとぶ","たかい" ]},
		{ "question": "買", "answers": [ "バイ","かう" ]},
		{ "question": "貸", "answers": [ "かす","タイ" ]},
		{ "question": "費", "answers": [ "ヒ","ついえる","ついやす" ]},
		{ "question": "貼", "answers": [ "チョウ","はる","テン","つける" ]},
		{ "question": "貿", "answers": [ "ボウ","あきなう" ]},
		{ "question": "賀", "answers": [ "ガ","よろこぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "賂", "answers": [ "ロ","まいない","まいなう" ]},
		{ "question": "賃", "answers": [ "チン","ジン","やとう" ]},
		{ "question": "賄", "answers": [ "ワイ","まかなう","カイ","まいなう" ]},
		{ "question": "資", "answers": [ "シ","たから","たすける","たち","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "賊", "answers": [ "ゾク","そこなう","わるもの" ]},
		{ "question": "賓", "answers": [ "ヒン","したがう","まろうど" ]},
		{ "question": "賛", "answers": [ "サン","たすける","たたえる","ほめる" ]},
		{ "question": "賜", "answers": [ "たまわる","シ","たまう","たまもの" ]},
		{ "question": "賞", "answers": [ "ショウ","ほめる","めでる" ]},
		{ "question": "賠", "answers": [ "バイ","つぐなう" ]},
		{ "question": "賢", "answers": [ "ケン","かしこい","さかしい","まさる" ]},
		{ "question": "賦", "answers": [ "フ","みつぎ","わかつ" ]},
		{ "question": "質", "answers": [ "シツ","シチ","チ","シ","ただす","たち","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "賭", "answers": [ "かける","ト","かけ" ]},
		{ "question": "購", "answers": [ "コウ","あがなう" ]},
		{ "question": "贈", "answers": [ "ソウ","ゾウ","おくる" ]},
		{ "question": "赤", "answers": [ "セキ","あか","あかい","あからむ","あからめる","シャク" ]},
		{ "question": "赦", "answers": [ "シャ","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "走", "answers": [ "ソウ","はしる" ]},
		{ "question": "赴", "answers": [ "フ","おもむく","つげる" ]},
		{ "question": "起", "answers": [ "キ","おきる","おこす","おこる","たつ" ]},
		{ "question": "超", "answers": [ "チョウ","こえる","こす" ]},
		{ "question": "越", "answers": [ "エツ","こえる","こす","オチ","オツ","こし" ]},
		{ "question": "趣", "answers": [ "シュ","おもむき","ソク","うながす","おもむく" ]},
		{ "question": "足", "answers": [ "ソク","あし","たす","たりる","たる" ]},
		{ "question": "距", "answers": [ "キョ","けづめ","ふせぐ","へだてる" ]},
		{ "question": "跡", "answers": [ "セキ","あと","シャク","あとかた" ]},
		{ "question": "路", "answers": [ "ロ","じ","くるま","みち" ]},
		{ "question": "跳", "answers": [ "チョウ","とぶ","はねる","トウ","おどる" ]},
		{ "question": "践", "answers": [ "セン","ふむ" ]},
		{ "question": "踊", "answers": [ "ヨウ","おどり","おどる" ]},
		{ "question": "踏", "answers": [ "トウ","ふまえる","ふむ" ]},
		{ "question": "踪", "answers": [ "ソウ","シュウ","あと" ]},
		{ "question": "蹴", "answers": [ "シュウ","ける","シュク" ]},
		{ "question": "躍", "answers": [ "ヤク","おどる","テキ" ]},
		{ "question": "身", "answers": [ "シン","み","みずから" ]},
		{ "question": "車", "answers": [ "シャ","くるま" ]},
		{ "question": "軌", "answers": [ "キ","わだち" ]},
		{ "question": "軍", "answers": [ "グン","クン","いくさ","つわもの" ]},
		{ "question": "軒", "answers": [ "ケン","のき","くるま","たかい","てすり","とぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "軟", "answers": [ "ナン","やわらか","やわらかい","ゼン","ネン" ]},
		{ "question": "転", "answers": [ "テン","ころがす","ころがる","ころげる","ころぶ","うたた","うつる","くるり","こける","まろぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "軸", "answers": [ "ジク","チク","しんぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "軽", "answers": [ "ケイ","かるい","かろやか","キン" ]},
		{ "question": "較", "answers": [ "カク","コウ","くらべる" ]},
		{ "question": "載", "answers": [ "サイ","のせる","のる","しるす","とし" ]},
		{ "question": "輝", "answers": [ "キ","かがやく","てる" ]},
		{ "question": "輩", "answers": [ "ハイ","ともがら","やから" ]},
		{ "question": "輪", "answers": [ "リン","わ" ]},
		{ "question": "輸", "answers": [ "ユ","シュ","いたす","うつす","おくる","まける" ]},
		{ "question": "轄", "answers": [ "カツ","くさび","とりしまる" ]},
		{ "question": "辛", "answers": [ "シン","からい","かのと","つらい" ]},
		{ "question": "辞", "answers": [ "ジ","やめる","ことば","ことわる" ]},
		{ "question": "辣", "answers": [ "ラツ","からい","きびしい","むごい" ]},
		{ "question": "辱", "answers": [ "ジョク","はずかしめる","ニク","かたじけない","はじ","はずかしめ" ]},
		{ "question": "農", "answers": [ "ノウ","ドウ","たがやす" ]},
		{ "question": "辺", "answers": [ "ヘン","あたり","べ","ほとり" ]},
		{ "question": "込", "answers": [ "こむ","こめる" ]},
		{ "question": "迅", "answers": [ "ジン","はげしい","はやい" ]},
		{ "question": "迎", "answers": [ "ゲイ","むかえる","ギョウ","ゴウ" ]},
		{ "question": "近", "answers": [ "キン","ちかい","コン" ]},
		{ "question": "返", "answers": [ "ヘン","かえす","かえる","ハン","ホン" ]},
		{ "question": "迫", "answers": [ "ハク","せまる","せる" ]},
		{ "question": "迭", "answers": [ "テツ","かわる","たがいに" ]},
		{ "question": "述", "answers": [ "ジュツ","のべる" ]},
		{ "question": "迷", "answers": [ "まよう","メイ","まどう" ]},
		{ "question": "追", "answers": [ "ツイ","おう" ]},
		{ "question": "退", "answers": [ "タイ","しりぞく","しりぞける","しさる","すさる","のく","のける","ひく" ]},
		{ "question": "送", "answers": [ "ソウ","おくる" ]},
		{ "question": "逃", "answers": [ "トウ","にがす","にげる","のがす","のがれる" ]},
		{ "question": "逆", "answers": [ "ギャク","さか","さからう","ゲキ","あらかじめ","むかえる" ]},
		{ "question": "透", "answers": [ "トウ","すかす","すく","すける","とおる" ]},
		{ "question": "逐", "answers": [ "チク","ジク","おう" ]},
		{ "question": "逓", "answers": [ "テイ","かわる","たがいに" ]},
		{ "question": "途", "answers": [ "ト","ズ","みち" ]},
		{ "question": "通", "answers": [ "ツウ","かよう","とおす","とおる","ツ" ]},
		{ "question": "逝", "answers": [ "セイ","いく","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "速", "answers": [ "ソク","はやい","はやまる","はやめる","すみやか" ]},
		{ "question": "造", "answers": [ "ゾウ","つくる","いたる","なる","はじめる","みやつこ" ]},
		{ "question": "連", "answers": [ "レン","つらなる","つらねる","つれる","しきりに" ]},
		{ "question": "逮", "answers": [ "タイ","テイ","およぶ","とらえる" ]},
		{ "question": "週", "answers": [ "シュウ","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "進", "answers": [ "シン","すすむ","すすめる" ]},
		{ "question": "逸", "answers": [ "イツ","イチ","うしなう","すぐれる","そらす","それる","はぐれる","はしる","はやる" ]},
		{ "question": "遂", "answers": [ "スイ","とげる","おおせる","ついに" ]},
		{ "question": "遅", "answers": [ "チ","おくらす","おくれる","おそい" ]},
		{ "question": "遇", "answers": [ "グウ","グ","あう","たまたま","もてなす" ]},
		{ "question": "遊", "answers": [ "ユウ","あそぶ","ユ","すさび","すさぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "運", "answers": [ "ウン","はこぶ","さだめ","めぐる" ]},
		{ "question": "遍", "answers": [ "ヘン","あまねく" ]},
		{ "question": "過", "answers": [ "カ","すぎる","すごす","あやまち","あやまつ","とが","よぎる" ]},
		{ "question": "道", "answers": [ "ドウ","みち","トウ","いう","みちびく" ]},
		{ "question": "達", "answers": [ "タツ","タチ","ダチ","たし","たち","とおる","とどく" ]},
		{ "question": "違", "answers": [ "イ","ちがう","ちがえる","かい","さる","たがう","たがえる","よこしま" ]},
		{ "question": "遜", "answers": [ "ソン","のがれる","へりくだる","ゆずる" ]},
		{ "question": "遠", "answers": [ "エン","とおい","オン","おち" ]},
		{ "question": "遡", "answers": [ "さかのぼる","ソ","むかう" ]},
		{ "question": "遣", "answers": [ "ケン","つかう","つかわす","やる" ]},
		{ "question": "適", "answers": [ "テキ","セキ","タク","かなう","たまたま","ゆく" ]},
		{ "question": "遭", "answers": [ "ソウ","あう" ]},
		{ "question": "遮", "answers": [ "シャ","さえぎる" ]},
		{ "question": "遵", "answers": [ "ジュン","シュン","したがう" ]},
		{ "question": "遷", "answers": [ "セン","うつす","うつる" ]},
		{ "question": "選", "answers": [ "セン","えらぶ","える","すぐる","よる" ]},
		{ "question": "遺", "answers": [ "イ","ユイ","すてる","のこす","のこる","わすれる" ]},
		{ "question": "避", "answers": [ "ヒ","さける","よける" ]},
		{ "question": "還", "answers": [ "カン","ゲン","かえす","かえる","また" ]},
		{ "question": "那", "answers": [ "ナ","ダ","いかんぞ","なに","なんぞ" ]},
		{ "question": "邦", "answers": [ "ホウ","くに" ]},
		{ "question": "邪", "answers": [ "ジャ","シャ","ヤ","よこしま" ]},
		{ "question": "邸", "answers": [ "テイ","やしき" ]},
		{ "question": "郊", "answers": [ "コウ" ]},
		{ "question": "郎", "answers": [ "ロウ","おとこ" ]},
		{ "question": "郡", "answers": [ "グン","クン","こおり" ]},
		{ "question": "部", "answers": [ "ブ","ホ","ホウ","くみ","すべる","つかさ","べ","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "郭", "answers": [ "カク","くるわ" ]},
		{ "question": "郵", "answers": [ "ユウ","しゅくば" ]},
		{ "question": "郷", "answers": [ "キョウ","ゴウ","さと" ]},
		{ "question": "都", "answers": [ "ツ","ト","みやこ","すべて" ]},
		{ "question": "酌", "answers": [ "シャク","くむ" ]},
		{ "question": "配", "answers": [ "ハイ","くばる","つれあい","ながす","ならぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "酎", "answers": [ "チュウ" ]},
		{ "question": "酒", "answers": [ "シュ","さか","さけ" ]},
		{ "question": "酔", "answers": [ "スイ","よう" ]},
		{ "question": "酢", "answers": [ "サク","す","ソ","すい" ]},
		{ "question": "酪", "answers": [ "ラク","ちちしる" ]},
		{ "question": "酬", "answers": [ "シュウ","むくいる" ]},
		{ "question": "酵", "answers": [ "コウ","こうじ","もと" ]},
		{ "question": "酷", "answers": [ "コク","きびしい","はなはだしい","ひどい","むごい" ]},
		{ "question": "酸", "answers": [ "サン","すい","す","つらい" ]},
		{ "question": "醒", "answers": [ "セイ","さます","さめる" ]},
		{ "question": "醜", "answers": [ "シュウ","みにくい","しこ","たぐい","にくむ" ]},
		{ "question": "醸", "answers": [ "ジョウ","かもす" ]},
		{ "question": "采", "answers": [ "サイ","いろどり","うね","すがた","とる" ]},
		{ "question": "釈", "answers": [ "シャク","セキ","おく","とかす","とく","ゆるす" ]},
		{ "question": "里", "answers": [ "リ","さと" ]},
		{ "question": "重", "answers": [ "ジュウ","チョウ","おもい","かさなる","かさねる","え","おもんじる" ]},
		{ "question": "野", "answers": [ "ヤ","の","ショ","いなかや","いやしい" ]},
		{ "question": "量", "answers": [ "リョウ","はかる","かさ","ちから" ]},
		{ "question": "金", "answers": [ "キン","コン","かな","かね","こがね" ]},
		{ "question": "釜", "answers": [ "かま","フ" ]},
		{ "question": "針", "answers": [ "シン","はり" ]},
		{ "question": "釣", "answers": [ "つる","チョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "鈍", "answers": [ "ドン","にぶい","にぶる","トン","なまる","にび","のろい" ]},
		{ "question": "鈴", "answers": [ "リン","レイ","すず" ]},
		{ "question": "鉄", "answers": [ "テツ","かね","くろがね" ]},
		{ "question": "鉛", "answers": [ "エン","なまり","おしろい" ]},
		{ "question": "鉢", "answers": [ "ハチ","ハツ" ]},
		{ "question": "鉱", "answers": [ "コウ","あらがね" ]},
		{ "question": "銀", "answers": [ "ギン","しろがね" ]},
		{ "question": "銃", "answers": [ "ジュウ","つつ" ]},
		{ "question": "銅", "answers": [ "ドウ","あかがね" ]},
		{ "question": "銘", "answers": [ "メイ","ミョウ","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "銭", "answers": [ "セン","ぜに","ゼン","すき" ]},
		{ "question": "鋭", "answers": [ "エイ","するどい","はやい" ]},
		{ "question": "鋳", "answers": [ "チュウ","いる","シュ" ]},
		{ "question": "鋼", "answers": [ "コウ","はがね" ]},
		{ "question": "錠", "answers": [ "ジョウ","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "錦", "answers": [ "キン","にしき" ]},
		{ "question": "錬", "answers": [ "レン","ねる" ]},
		{ "question": "錮", "answers": [ "コ","かたい","ながわずらい","ふさぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "錯", "answers": [ "サク","ソ","あやまる","おく","まじる" ]},
		{ "question": "録", "answers": [ "ロク","リョ","リョク","しるす" ]},
		{ "question": "鍋", "answers": [ "なべ","カ" ]},
		{ "question": "鍛", "answers": [ "タン","きたえる" ]},
		{ "question": "鍵", "answers": [ "ケン","かぎ" ]},
		{ "question": "鎌", "answers": [ "かま","レン" ]},
		{ "question": "鎖", "answers": [ "サ","くさり","さす","とざす" ]},
		{ "question": "鎮", "answers": [ "チン","しずまる","しずめる","テン","おさえ" ]},
		{ "question": "鏡", "answers": [ "キョウ","かがみ" ]},
		{ "question": "鐘", "answers": [ "ショウ","かね","シュ" ]},
		{ "question": "鑑", "answers": [ "カン","かんがみる","かがみ" ]},
		{ "question": "長", "answers": [ "チョウ","ながい","ジョウ","おさ","たける" ]},
		{ "question": "門", "answers": [ "モン","かど","ボン","いえ","と","みうち" ]},
		{ "question": "閉", "answers": [ "ヘイ","しまる","しめる","とじる","とざす","たてる" ]},
		{ "question": "開", "answers": [ "カイ","あく","あける","ひらく","ひらける","はだかる","はだける" ]},
		{ "question": "閑", "answers": [ "カン","しずか","ならう","ひま" ]},
		{ "question": "間", "answers": [ "カン","ケン","あいだ","ま","あい","うかがう","しずか","はざま","ひそかに" ]},
		{ "question": "関", "answers": [ "カン","かかわる","せき","からくり","かんぬき" ]},
		{ "question": "閣", "answers": [ "カク","たかどの","たな" ]},
		{ "question": "閥", "answers": [ "バツ","ハツ","いえがら","いさお" ]},
		{ "question": "閲", "answers": [ "エツ","けみする","へる" ]},
		{ "question": "闇", "answers": [ "やみ","アン","くらい" ]},
		{ "question": "闘", "answers": [ "トウ","たたかう","たたかい" ]},
		{ "question": "阜", "answers": [ "フ","おか","ゆたか" ]},
		{ "question": "阪", "answers": [ "ハン","さか" ]},
		{ "question": "防", "answers": [ "ボウ","ふせぐ","ホウ","まもる" ]},
		{ "question": "阻", "answers": [ "ソ","はばむ","けわしい","へだたる" ]},
		{ "question": "附", "answers": [ "フ","ブ","つく","つける" ]},
		{ "question": "降", "answers": [ "コウ","おりる","おろす","ふる","ゴウ","くだす","くだる" ]},
		{ "question": "限", "answers": [ "ゲン","かぎる","かぎり","きり" ]},
		{ "question": "陛", "answers": [ "ヘイ","きざはし" ]},
		{ "question": "院", "answers": [ "イン","かき","かこい" ]},
		{ "question": "陣", "answers": [ "ジン","チン","じんだて" ]},
		{ "question": "除", "answers": [ "ジョ","のぞく","ジ","つきる","のける","はらう","よける" ]},
		{ "question": "陥", "answers": [ "カン","おちいる","おとしいれる" ]},
		{ "question": "陪", "answers": [ "バイ","したがう" ]},
		{ "question": "陰", "answers": [ "イン","かげ","かげる","アン","オン","くもる","くらい","ひそか" ]},
		{ "question": "陳", "answers": [ "チン","ジン","つらねる","のべる","ひねる","ふるい" ]},
		{ "question": "陵", "answers": [ "リョウ","みささぎ","おか","しのぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "陶", "answers": [ "トウ","ヨウ","すえ" ]},
		{ "question": "陸", "answers": [ "リク","ロク","おか","くが" ]},
		{ "question": "険", "answers": [ "ケン","けわしい" ]},
		{ "question": "陽", "answers": [ "ヨウ","いつわる","ひ","ひなた" ]},
		{ "question": "隅", "answers": [ "グウ","すみ" ]},
		{ "question": "隆", "answers": [ "リュウ","さかん","たかい" ]},
		{ "question": "隊", "answers": [ "タイ","ツイ","おちる","くみ" ]},
		{ "question": "階", "answers": [ "カイ","きざはし","しな","はしご" ]},
		{ "question": "随", "answers": [ "ズイ","したがう" ]},
		{ "question": "隔", "answers": [ "カク","へだたる","へだてる" ]},
		{ "question": "隙", "answers": [ "すき","ゲキ","ケキ","ひま" ]},
		{ "question": "際", "answers": [ "サイ","きわ","あい","まじわる" ]},
		{ "question": "障", "answers": [ "ショウ","さわる","ふせぐ","へだてる" ]},
		{ "question": "隠", "answers": [ "イン","かくす","かくれる","オン" ]},
		{ "question": "隣", "answers": [ "リン","となり","となる" ]},
		{ "question": "隷", "answers": [ "レイ","したがう","しもべ" ]},
		{ "question": "隻", "answers": [ "セキ","ひとつ" ]},
		{ "question": "雄", "answers": [ "ユウ","お","おす","おん","まさる" ]},
		{ "question": "雅", "answers": [ "ガ","ア","つね","みやび","みやびやか" ]},
		{ "question": "集", "answers": [ "シュウ","あつまる","あつめる","つどう","すだく","たかる" ]},
		{ "question": "雇", "answers": [ "コ","やとう" ]},
		{ "question": "雌", "answers": [ "シ","め","めす","めん" ]},
		{ "question": "雑", "answers": [ "ザツ","ゾウ","まじる","まぜる" ]},
		{ "question": "離", "answers": [ "リ","はなす","はなれる","レイ","かかる","かる","つく","ならぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "難", "answers": [ "ナン","むずかしい","かたい","ダ","ダン","ナ","にくい","むつかしい" ]},
		{ "question": "雨", "answers": [ "ウ","あま","あめ" ]},
		{ "question": "雪", "answers": [ "セツ","ゆき","すすぐ","そそぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "雰", "answers": [ "フン","きり" ]},
		{ "question": "雲", "answers": [ "ウン","くも","そら" ]},
		{ "question": "零", "answers": [ "レイ","あまり","おちる","こぼれる","ゼロ","ふる" ]},
		{ "question": "雷", "answers": [ "ライ","かみなり","いかずち" ]},
		{ "question": "電", "answers": [ "デン","テン","いなずま" ]},
		{ "question": "需", "answers": [ "ジュ","もとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "震", "answers": [ "シン","ふるう","ふるえる" ]},
		{ "question": "霊", "answers": [ "レイ","リョウ","たま","たましい","よい" ]},
		{ "question": "霜", "answers": [ "しも","ソウ" ]},
		{ "question": "霧", "answers": [ "ム","きり","ブ" ]},
		{ "question": "露", "answers": [ "ロ","ロウ","つゆ","あらわ","あらわす","あらわれる" ]},
		{ "question": "青", "answers": [ "セイ","あお","あおい","ショウ" ]},
		{ "question": "静", "answers": [ "セイ","しず","しずか","しずまる","しずめる","ジョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "非", "answers": [ "ヒ","あらず","そしる","わるい" ]},
		{ "question": "面", "answers": [ "メン","おも","おもて","つら","ベン","そむく","も" ]},
		{ "question": "革", "answers": [ "カク","かわ","キョク","あらたまる","あらためる" ]},
		{ "question": "靴", "answers": [ "くつ","カ" ]},
		{ "question": "韓", "answers": [ "カン","いげた","から" ]},
		{ "question": "音", "answers": [ "オン","おと","ね","イン","たより" ]},
		{ "question": "韻", "answers": [ "イン","おもむき","ひびき" ]},
		{ "question": "響", "answers": [ "キョウ","ひびく","どよめく" ]},
		{ "question": "頂", "answers": [ "チョウ","いただき","いただく","テイ" ]},
		{ "question": "頃", "answers": [ "ころ","キ","キョウ","ケイ","かたあし","しばらく" ]},
		{ "question": "項", "answers": [ "コウ","うなじ" ]},
		{ "question": "順", "answers": [ "ジュン","したがう","すなお" ]},
		{ "question": "須", "answers": [ "ス","シュ","しばらく","すべからく","まつ","もちいる","もとめる" ]},
		{ "question": "預", "answers": [ "ヨ","あずかる","あずける","あらかじめ" ]},
		{ "question": "頑", "answers": [ "ガン","かたくな" ]},
		{ "question": "頒", "answers": [ "ハン","フン","しく","まだら","わける" ]},
		{ "question": "頓", "answers": [ "トン","トツ","くるしむ","つかれる","つまずく","とどまる","とみに","ぬかずく","ひたぶる" ]},
		{ "question": "領", "answers": [ "リョウ","うなじ","えり","うける","おさめる","かしら","かなめ" ]},
		{ "question": "頭", "answers": [ "ズ","トウ","あたま","かしら","ト","ジュウ","かぶり","かみ","こうべ","ほとり" ]},
		{ "question": "頰", "answers": [ "ほお","キョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "頻", "answers": [ "ヒン","ビン","しきりに","しきる" ]},
		{ "question": "頼", "answers": [ "ライ","たのむ","たのもしい","たよる","たより" ]},
		{ "question": "題", "answers": [ "ダイ","テイ","ひたい" ]},
		{ "question": "額", "answers": [ "ガク","ひたい","ぬか","ぬかずく" ]},
		{ "question": "顎", "answers": [ "ガク","あご" ]},
		{ "question": "顔", "answers": [ "ガン","かお","かんばせ" ]},
		{ "question": "顕", "answers": [ "ケン","あきらか","あらわす","あらわれる" ]},
		{ "question": "願", "answers": [ "ガン","ねがう","ねがわくは" ]},
		{ "question": "類", "answers": [ "ルイ","たぐい","たぐえる","にる" ]},
		{ "question": "顧", "answers": [ "コ","かえりみる" ]},
		{ "question": "風", "answers": [ "フウ","かざ","かぜ","フ","すがた","ならわし","ふり" ]},
		{ "question": "飛", "answers": [ "ヒ","とばす","とぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "食", "answers": [ "ショク","くう","たべる","ジキ","くらう","イ","シ","はむ" ]},
		{ "question": "飢", "answers": [ "キ","うえる","うえ" ]},
		{ "question": "飯", "answers": [ "ハン","めし","いい","くらう","まま" ]},
		{ "question": "飲", "answers": [ "イン","のむ","オン","のます","みずかう" ]},
		{ "question": "飼", "answers": [ "シ","かう","やしなう" ]},
		{ "question": "飽", "answers": [ "ホウ","あかす","あきる" ]},
		{ "question": "飾", "answers": [ "ショク","かざる","かざり" ]},
		{ "question": "餅", "answers": [ "ヘイ","もち" ]},
		{ "question": "養", "answers": [ "ヨウ","やしなう","やしない" ]},
		{ "question": "餌", "answers": [ "え","えさ","ジ","くう","たべもの" ]},
		{ "question": "餓", "answers": [ "ガ","うえ","うえる" ]},
		{ "question": "館", "answers": [ "カン","やかた","たち","たて" ]},
		{ "question": "首", "answers": [ "シュ","くび","かしら","こうべ","はじめ","もうす" ]},
		{ "question": "香", "answers": [ "コウ","か","かおり","かおる","キョウ","かぐわしい","かんばしい" ]},
		{ "question": "馬", "answers": [ "バ","うま","ま","マ","メ" ]},
		{ "question": "駄", "answers": [ "ダ","タ","のせる" ]},
		{ "question": "駅", "answers": [ "エキ","うまや" ]},
		{ "question": "駆", "answers": [ "ク","かける","かる","おう" ]},
		{ "question": "駐", "answers": [ "チュウ","チュ","とどまる" ]},
		{ "question": "駒", "answers": [ "こま","ク" ]},
		{ "question": "騎", "answers": [ "キ","のる" ]},
		{ "question": "騒", "answers": [ "ソウ","さわぐ","うれい","ざわつく","ぞめく" ]},
		{ "question": "験", "answers": [ "ケン","ゲン","あかし","しるし","ためす" ]},
		{ "question": "騰", "answers": [ "トウ","あがる","のぼる" ]},
		{ "question": "驚", "answers": [ "キョウ","おどろかす","おどろく" ]},
		{ "question": "骨", "answers": [ "コツ","ほね" ]},
		{ "question": "骸", "answers": [ "ガイ","カイ","ほね","むくろ" ]},
		{ "question": "髄", "answers": [ "ズイ" ]},
		{ "question": "高", "answers": [ "コウ","たか","たかい","たかまる","たかめる" ]},
		{ "question": "髪", "answers": [ "ハツ","かみ","ホツ" ]},
		{ "question": "鬱", "answers": [ "ウツ","さかん","しげる","ふさぐ" ]},
		{ "question": "鬼", "answers": [ "キ","おに" ]},
		{ "question": "魂", "answers": [ "コン","たましい","たま" ]},
		{ "question": "魅", "answers": [ "ミ","ビ","すだま","もののけ" ]},
		{ "question": "魔", "answers": [ "マ","バ" ]},
		{ "question": "魚", "answers": [ "ギョ","うお","さかな" ]},
		{ "question": "鮮", "answers": [ "セン","あざやか","あたらしい","すくない" ]},
		{ "question": "鯨", "answers": [ "ゲイ","くじら","ケイ" ]},
		{ "question": "鳥", "answers": [ "チョウ","とり" ]},
		{ "question": "鳴", "answers": [ "メイ","なく","ならす","なる","ミョウ" ]},
		{ "question": "鶏", "answers": [ "ケイ","にわとり","とり" ]},
		{ "question": "鶴", "answers": [ "つる","カク" ]},
		{ "question": "鹿", "answers": [ "か","しか","ロク" ]},
		{ "question": "麓", "answers": [ "ロク","ふもと" ]},
		{ "question": "麗", "answers": [ "レイ","うるわしい","リ","うらら","うららか","つらなる","ならぶ" ]},
		{ "question": "麦", "answers": [ "むぎ","バク" ]},
		{ "question": "麺", "answers": [ "メン","ベン","むぎこ" ]},
		{ "question": "麻", "answers": [ "マ","あさ","バ","しびれる" ]},
		{ "question": "黄", "answers": [ "オウ","き","コウ","こ" ]},
		{ "question": "黒", "answers": [ "コク","くろ","くろい" ]},
		{ "question": "黙", "answers": [ "モク","だまる","ボク","だんまり","もだす" ]},
		{ "question": "鼓", "answers": [ "コ","つづみ" ]},
		{ "question": "鼻", "answers": [ "はな","ビ","はじめ" ]},
		{ "question": "齢", "answers": [ "レイ","とし","よわい" ]}
	]
}
